<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>HOD2and3RETURN</title>
      <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/</link>
      <description>The House of The Dead</description>
      <language>ja</language>
      <copyright>Copyright 2008</copyright>
      <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 08:02:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
      <generator>http://www.sixapart.com/movabletype/</generator>
      <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs> 

            <item>
         <title>IN CLOSING　NEW!</title>
         <description><![CDATA[Now I’ve told you everything I have to tell.
<BR>
In these battles where a split-second’s hesitation could mean 
the difference between life and death, I’m sure the things you’ve 
learned from this file will help keep you alive.
<BR>
But just because you’ve learned a thing or two here, don’t think 
you can go in cocky. There are some things you can only learn on 
the actual battleground.
<BR>
And remember that the strategies I’ve written here are only one 
way to go about things. There are lots of other strategies that might 
fit your skills and style better.
<BR>
Finding the strategies that are right for you is the only way you’ll 
ever become a true AMS agent.
<BR>
Good luck, and continue to hone those skills.
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/in_closing.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/in_closing.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">IN CLOSING</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 08:02:21 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>THE EMPEROR　NEW!</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<img alt="BOSS6.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/BOSS6.jpg" width="260" height="347" />
The Emperor is Goldman’s terrifying creation, designed 
to rule over all of nature. Its weak point is <strong>the red core</strong> 
that can be seen in the center of its transparent body.
<BR>
<strong>Unlike other bosses, each shot you land can whittle away 
at the Emperor’s health, </strong>so the accuracy and speed you’ve 
cultivated up until this point will really be tested here. 
<BR>
The Emperor’s attack patterns can be broadly divided into three types.
<BR>
<strong><u>[1]Orb Attacks</u></strong>
The Emperor will randomly use one of three types of orb attacks: 
firing orbs one at a time, firing multiple orbs at once, and a 
rush-and-slash attack.

Firing Orbs One at a Time
<img alt="EMPEROR_02.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/EMPEROR_02.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Just before it attacks, the Emperor will thrust one of its hands 
forward. The orbs will move at different speeds, depending on 
the difficulty level, so watch out. These orbs can be shot down 
with one bullet each, so try to remain calm and deal with them 
one by one.
<BR>
Firing Multiple Orbs at Once
<img alt="EMPEROR_03.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/EMPEROR_03.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Just before the Emperor fires multiple orbs at once, it will thrust 
both of its hands forward. The orbs will always move at the same 
speed in this attack, regardless of difficulty level.
<BR>
Rush-and-Slash Attack
<img alt="EMPEROR_04_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/EMPEROR_04_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Before the Emperor makes a rush-and-slash attack, it charges 
up its energy in order to transform its orbs into a sword. <strong>That’s 
the best time to get lots of shots in. </strong>And if you repeatedly fire 
at its core while it has its sword raised, you’ll be able to stop 
the attack.
<BR>
<strong><u>
[2]Transformation Attacks</u></strong>
Once you’ve reduced the Emperor’s health by about thirty 
percent, its attack pattern will change, and it’ll start transforming 
its orbs into the bosses you met previously in the game.
<BR>
Judgment Transformation
<img alt="EMPEROR_06_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/EMPEROR_06_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
If you manage to hit the Emperor’s core while it’s charging up, 
the orbs will always transform into Judgment. In this stage, 
Judgment won’t use its circling-left/right attack, so <strong>you should 
simply fire repeatedly into the center of its flight pattern.</strong>
<BR>
Hierophant Transformation
<img alt="EMPEROR_07_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/EMPEROR_07_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
The Hierophant will jump high into the air and try to stab you 
with its trident. <strong>In this stage, its chest will always remain open, 
so you can just aim for its core and keep shooting. </strong>This 
transformation is probably the easiest to deal with of the four.
<BR>
Tower Transformation
<img alt="EMPEROR_08_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/EMPEROR_08_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
After Tower leans its neck to the right, it’ll come slanting down 
toward you for a bite, so the key is to gun for the moment it starts 
to lean. <strong>Be sure to take aim in advance above and to the right of 
the Emperor and fire repeatedly when the Tower starts to move.</strong>
<BR>
Strength Transformation
<img alt="EMPEROR_09_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/EMPEROR_09_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<strong>The key to defeating Strength is to aim more for its forehead 
than for the center of its head. </strong>The only time you’ll be able to 
land your shots is when Strength swings its chainsaw up, so 
timing is more critical with this transformation than with the 
others. Of the four transformations, this one is probably the 
most difficult to deal with.
<BR>
<strong><u>[3]Orbiting Attack</u></strong>
<img alt="EMPEROR_10_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/EMPEROR_10_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
When the Emperor’s health falls to approximately one-third, 
it becomes just a core, and it’ll charge at you with its orbs 
spinning around it at high speed. 
<BR>
The core is small, so it’ll take accuracy to hit it, but if you 
stay calm and aim carefully, you should be able to handle this 
attack fairly easily. Once you’ve gotten this far, you’ve all 
but beaten the game!
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/the_emperor.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/the_emperor.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">HOD2</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>WHEEL OF FATE　NEW!</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<img alt="zb05_st6_crystal.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/zb05_st6_crystal.jpg" width="260" height="347" />
The Wheel of Fate’s weak point is <strong>the glowing white 
symbol in the center of its chest. </strong>Not only is this weak 
point very small, but your bullets will just ricochet off 
when the Wheel of Fate has its back turned or when 
its wheel gets in the way, so it’s going to be tough to 
land hits.
<BR>
Because the Wheel of Fate has so many different attack 
patterns, you’re going to need it all in order to survive: 
speed, accuracy and precision timing of your reloads.
You also have to be able to tell what attack is coming 
next just by watching the Wheel of Fate’s movements, 
and be prepared for that attack.
<BR>
The Wheel of Fate has five attack patterns. At first, it 
will switch between Attack Patterns 1, 2 and 3 at random. 
When its health drops to half, though, it’ll use its light 
sphere attack. When its health falls to one-quarter or 
less, it releases its lightning bolt attack.
<BR>
<strong><u>[1]Throws rings of light at you.</u></strong>
<img alt="WheelOfFate_01.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/WheelOfFate_01.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<strong>While the Wheel of Fate charges up energy, it curls itself 
up and conceals its weak point, so you won’t be able to 
get any shots in. </strong>Just steel yourself and get ready for your 
chance to attack.
<BR>
Once the Wheel of Fate starts firing its rings of light, it’s 
time to start shooting. These rings will approach you from 
the center, arcing left and right.
<BR>
<strong>First of all, aim for the center and quickly fire all six of your 
shots. Then immediately reload and take care of any rings 
you missed.</strong> If you get the chance, also try to hit the Wheel 
of Fate itself, which will be far back in the center.
<BR>
<strong><u>[2]Body-slams you.</u></strong>
<img alt="WheelOfFate_02.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/WheelOfFate_02.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
During this attack, the Wheel of Fate will approach you 
directly, so it should be easy to target. <strong>But even if you 
land all six shots perfectly, you still won’t be able to drive 
the Wheel of Fate back.</strong>
<BR>
You’ll have to alternate quickly between shooting as fast 
as you can, reloading, and shooting as fast as you can again.
<BR>
<strong>To avoid having to reload needlessly, wait until the Wheel 
of Fate faces your way, and then get your shots in all at 
once when it draws near.</strong>
<BR>
<strong><u>[3] Flies around at high speed.</u></strong>
<img alt="WheelOfFate_03.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/WheelOfFate_03.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
This attack will test your marksmanship. You’ll have to 
try to hit the Wheel of Fate’s tiny weak point as it goes 
zipping around at high speed.
<BR>
The Wheel of Fate’s wheel will obstruct its weak point, 
and the boss will turn its back on you sometimes, too, 
so there won’t be many opportunities to get your shots in.
<BR>
<strong>So that you don’t waste the precious few chances you 
do get by being out of bullets, avoid shooting repeatedly, </strong>
and track the Wheel of Fate’s movements carefully with 
your eyes.
<BR>
If you’re having trouble tracking it while it’s moving 
around so fast, you could try just targeting the times
when it pauses for an instant, but be prepared to take 
some damage.
<BR>
At the end of this attack, the Wheel of Fate will try to 
hit you with a body slam. 
<img alt="WheelOfFate_04.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/WheelOfFate_04.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<strong>At the last instant of its approach, it’ll be at point-blank 
range, so it’s a great chance to do some major damage. </strong>
So even if it gets really close, keep shooting and don’t 
give up.
<BR>
<strong><u>[4]Shoots light spheres at you.</u></strong>
<img alt="WheelOfFate_05.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/WheelOfFate_05.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
While the Wheel of Fate is busy making its light spheres, 
try to get as many shots into its weak point as you can. 
Reload when it starts shooting those spheres at you from 
its wheel, and take care of them quickly as they come 
flying toward you.
<BR>
Because the light spheres move fairly slowly, you’ll probably 
be tempted to get in some shots at the Wheel of Fate itself 
during the intervals, but if you press your luck like that, you’ll 
quickly end up taking unnecessary damage from the light spheres.
<BR>
So ignore the Wheel of Fate for now, and just concentrate on 
the light spheres. You can go back to targeting the Wheel of 
Fate’s weak point once you’ve wiped out all of the spheres.
<BR>
<strong><u>[5]Fires lightning bolts at you.</u></strong>
<img alt="WheelOfFate_06.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/WheelOfFate_06.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Once you get this far, you’re almost home free.
At the beginning, <strong>focus all of your attention on firing at the 
Wheel of Fate’s weak point as many times as you can until it 
releases its lightning bolts. </strong>
<BR>
<strong>Once it does, reload just as you are turning around and start 
shooting those lightning bolts down immediately.</strong>
<img alt="WheelOfFate_07.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/WheelOfFate_07.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
There’ll be a lot of lightning bolts to deal with, so <strong>start shooting 
in areas where they’re closely clumped together to pare down 
their numbers a little. </strong>After that, take care of any lightning bolts 
you missed one by one.
<BR>
Sure, there’ll be a lot of lightning bolts, but they won’t be 
very fast. If you stay calm and just keep shooting the ones 
closest to you, you won’t have all that much trouble shooting 
them all down.
<BR>
Once you’ve wiped out all of the lightning bolts, you’ll turn 
to face the Wheel of Fate once more. Start firing at it again 
with everything you’ve got and make victory yours!
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/wheel_of_fate.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/wheel_of_fate.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">HODIII</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>THE SUN</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<img alt="zb03_st3bossroom2.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/zb03_st3bossroom2.jpg" width="260" height="347" />
The Sun is a hideous, tree-like monster with countless faces 
all over its trunk. Its weak points are <strong>its flowers, the tips of its 
vines, and the tips of its roots.</strong>
<BR>
You can also do a little bit of damage to the Sun by shooting the 
countless faces on its trunk.
<strong>After you prevent each of the Sun’s attacks, go back to shooting 
those faces non-stop.</strong>

<img alt="Sun_01.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Sun_01.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
The Sun will first attack you with either its vines or its roots. 
When its health drops to half or less, it’ll start attacking you by 
either using pollen or by stretching out one of its heads at you.
<BR>
The Sun has four attack patterns.
<BR>
<u><strong>[1]Sends its vines to attack you.</strong></u>
<img alt="Sun_02.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Sun_02.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Each of the Sun’s vines has its own health bar, and they’ll 
keep attacking you without mercy unless you defeat them all. 
As soon as you’ve taken care of one, aim for the next one 
immediately and get to work.
<BR>
And by the way, when there are only two vines, they’ll each 
have more health than when there were three vines, so be 
on your toes.
<BR>
<strong><u>[2]Sends its roots to attack you.</u></strong>
<img alt="Sun_03.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Sun_03.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Sometimes the Sun’s roots will attack you one at a time, and 
sometimes they’ll come in twos.
<BR>
<strong>You can inflict damage on these roots even while they’re still 
underground, </strong>so make sure you shave down their health as much 
as possible before they pop up. 
<BR>
After that, the safest thing to do is <strong>to try to time your shots 
so that you’ll blow the roots away as soon as they appear 
aboveground.</strong>
<img alt="Sun_04.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Sun_04.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
<strong><u>[3]Spits pollen at you.</u></strong>
<img alt="Sun_05.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Sun_05.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
During this attack, <strong>you can get a little bit of damage in 
even before the flower opens,</strong> so concentrate on shooting 
the flower as fast as you can before it spits pollen at you.
<BR>
Once the flower spews its pollen, quickly reload and 
deal with the pollen itself.
<BR>
Each pollen grain can be brought down with one shot, 
but because there are so many of them, and because 
they scatter all over the screen, you’ll most likely 
take some damage if you just fire at random.
<BR>
<strong>As soon as the pollen grains spew out, and before 
they have a chance to scatter, fire all six of your shots 
into the upper, central part of the screen to cut down 
on their numbers. </strong>After that, you can deal with each 
of the pollen grains you missed one by one.
<BR>
<strong><u>[4]Stretches out one of its heads at you.</u></strong>
<img alt="Sun_06.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Sun_06.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
During this attack, the Sun will stretch out one of its heads 
into fairly close range, so it’s the perfect opportunity to do 
some serious damage. But you won’t have much time before 
the head attacks, so<strong> just keep shooting rapid-fire and try to 
make it retreat.</strong>
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/the_sun.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/the_sun.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">HODIII</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 07:42:07 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>THE MAGICIAN</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<img alt="BOSS5.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/BOSS5.jpg" width="260" height="347" />
The Magician is one of Dr. Curien’s masterpieces, a powerful 
creature that can control fire. It was thought to have been 
laid to rest during the Curien Mansion incident...
<BR>
The Magician’s weak points are the four areas not covered 
by armor: <strong>its upper left arm, its lower right arm, its left thigh, 
and its right shin.</strong> Attacks anywhere other than on its weak 
points do no damage whatsoever. 
<BR>
<strong>The weak points on its legs leave larger areas exposed and 
move around less, so they’re easier to target than the ones 
on its arms.</strong>
<BR>
The Magician has two basic attack patterns.
<BR>
<strong><u>[1]Fireballs</u></strong>
The Magician will shoot balls of fire from its hands. <strong>You should 
fire repeatedly at the Magician’s weak points while it’s charging 
up energy, </strong>
<img alt="MAGICIAN_02_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/MAGICIAN_02_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
<strong>and then, once it releases its fireballs, you should concentrate 
on shooting these projectiles down. </strong>
<img alt="MAGICIAN_03_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/MAGICIAN_03_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
Fireballs can be brought down with only one shot each, so you 
should be able to handle them, now that you’ve come this far 
in the game.
<BR>
<strong><u>[2]Flaming Punch</u></strong>
The Magician will charge you with its arm engulfed in flames. 
Whether or not you can handle this attack will be the difference 
between life and death. If you can hit one of the Magician’s weak 
points, it’ll stop the attack, so <strong>your best bet is to quickly aim 
for either its left thigh or right shin as soon as the Magician 
starts its dash.</strong>
<img alt="MAGICIAN_04_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/MAGICIAN_04_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
Once the Magician’s health drops below fifty percent, it’ll fly up 
and start raining fireballs down on you without mercy. Of the ten 
fireballs it shoots from its hands, <strong>only the five in the middle can 
actually hit you, so concentrate only on shooting those down. </strong>
How rapidly you can fire counts for a lot here, so give it all you’ve got!
<BR>
The Magician is defenseless while it’s charging up energy, 
so <strong>aim for its right shin and concentrate your firepower there.</strong>
<img alt="MAGICIAN_06_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/MAGICIAN_06_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/the_magician.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/the_magician.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">HOD2</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 06:50:12 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>THE FOOL</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<img alt="zb02_st2net.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/zb02_st2net.jpg" width="260" height="347" />
The Fool is a huge, sloth-like monster. But despite its appearance, 
it can attack with surprisingly nimble movements. <strong>Its weak points 
are its right hand, right foot, left hand, and left foot.</strong>
<BR>
Unlike other bosses, the current weak point (one of the Fool’s 
hands or feet) will be marked throughout your battle against this 
boss, so you’ll be able to tell at a glance what you should be 
aiming for.
<BR>
But the Fool’s weak points are small, and move around quite 
a bit as the boss moves. And to top it all off, unless you keep hitting 
these weak points <strong>dead center</strong>, you won’t do much damage.
<BR>
What you need when you go up against the Fool is accuracy and 
quick marksmanship. Aim carefully at the weak point mark and never 
lose your focus.
<BR>
The Fool has six attack patterns.
<BR>
<strong><u>[1]Claws at you with its right hand.</u></strong>
<img alt="Fool_01.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Fool_01.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
During this attack, the Fool doesn’t move all that much, so 
it ought to be pretty easy to target its weak point. If it manages 
to hit you at this point, you probably won’t have much luck 
beating it. Just keep your cool and deal with the Fool calmly here.
<BR>
<strong><u>[2]Claws at you with its left foot.</u></strong>
<img alt="Fool_02_take2.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Fool_02_take2.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
During this attack, the Fool’s weak point, its left foot, will 
swing left and right in the area diagonally down and to the 
right of the center of its body. <strong>Your field of vision will sometimes 
be obstructed by the stairs, but you’ll still be able to get some 
damage in even then.</strong> Just stay focused and keep shooting.
<BR>
<strong><u>[3]Drops corpses on you.</u></strong>
<img alt="Fool_03.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Fool_03.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Corpses will rain down on you from above one after another, but 
if you just concentrate on firing into the center of the group 
of bodies, you should make out all right. <strong>The corpses that drop 
at the outer edges of your field of vision will miss you, so ignore 
them and just concentrate on taking care of the ones in the center.</strong>
<BR>
<strong><u>[4]Claws at you with its right foot.</u></strong>
<img alt="Fool_04.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Fool_04.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
The right foot weak point will swing from the center right to 
the center left as the Fool’s hip pivots. It won’t move all that 
fast, so if you keep a level head and keep shooting, that ought 
to do the trick.
<BR>
<strong><u>[5]Claws at you with its left hand.</u></strong>
<img alt="Fool_05_take2.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Fool_05_take2.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
During this attack, the Fool will climb toward you along the cage, 
making big movements with both hands. Its left hand weak point 
will be swinging violently, so it’ll be tough to keep your sight on it. 
<strong>Just aim for either the left or the right end of the hand’s swinging 
arc.</strong>
<BR>
<strong><u>[6]Jumps at you.</u></strong>
<img alt="Fool_06.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Fool_06.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
During this attack, the only chance you’ll have to attack is the 
tiny fraction of time when the boss is in the air and is about to 
attack you. <strong>And you won’t have any time to reload during that 
moment, either. On top of all that, you won’t be able to stop the 
Fool’s attack unless you land all six of your shots, either. </strong>This 
attack pattern is a tough one.
<BR>
Reload before the Fool jumps, and place your shots carefully, 
<strong>aiming a little to the left of and above the center for the first 
shot, and then shifting your sight down slightly</strong> with each of 
your next shots.
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/the_fool.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/the_fool.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">HODIII</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 07:32:19 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>STRENGTH</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<img alt="BOSS4.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/BOSS4.jpg" width="260" height="347" />
Strength is a huge, chainsaw-wielding zombie. Its weak point 
is <strong>its head</strong>, but because it blocks your shots with its 
chainsaw, it’s extremely difficult to hit. You can slowly
 wear away at Strength’s health by shooting its body, too, 
but that won’t stop Strength's forward movement, so it’s 
probably best just to aim for its head.
<BR>
Strength’s attack patterns can be broadly divided into three types.
<BR>
<strong><u>[1]Chainsaw Slash</u></strong>
Strength will rush at you with tremendous force and try to 
slash you with its chainsaw. There’s no other way to stop 
it except to aim at its head and fire repeatedly. When shooting, 
it’s best to aim <strong>slightly to one side rather than at the center 
of its head, </strong>
<img alt="screenshot_078_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/screenshot_078_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
and you should try to avoid hitting its chainsaw.
<BR>
<strong><u>[2]Hatchet Throw</u></strong>
<img alt="STRENGTH_04_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/STRENGTH_04_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Strength will attack you by throwing hatchets that’ve been 
embedded in its body. The hatches will fly at you in an arc. 
Shoot them down and then go back to firing at Strength’s head.
<BR>
<strong><u>[3]Jump Down and Slash</u></strong>
Strength will jump down from the tops of walls and try to slash 
you. Just before it lands, you’ll have a chance to shoot its head, 
but the window of opportunity is extremely narrow. The key is to 
aim for<strong> its chin area as soon as it jumps and to fire repeatedly.</strong>
<img alt="STRENGTH_06_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/STRENGTH_06_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
At times, Strength will threaten you with its chainsaw raised 
menacingly. It leaves itself wide open when it does this, so fire at 
its head relentlessly.
<img alt="STRENGTH_08_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/STRENGTH_08_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
Depending on what route you took, your battleground will either 
be the east side or the west side of the coliseum, but the basic 
strategy will be the same.
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/strength.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/strength.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">HOD2</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 06:43:47 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>DEATH</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<img alt="zb01_st4aisle2.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/zb01_st4aisle2.jpg" width="260" height="347" />
Death is a brutal guard that chases you relentlessly 
with a gigantic club. Shooting its big, brawny body won’t 
do you any good. <strong>Aim for its head.</strong> That’s its weak point. 
<BR>
If you don’t cause enough damage to it before it closes in, 
you’ll fall victim to its giant club.
<img alt="Death_00_take2.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Death_00_take2.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
You’ll be fighting Death twice, but the basic strategies are 
the same both times. You have to be careful the second time 
it appears, though, because it'll be chasing you behind obstacles, 
passing in and out of view. Efficient timing of your reloads is key.
<BR>
Death has two attack patterns.
<BR>
<strong><u>[1]Charges toward you and wallops you.</u></strong>
Death’s weak point, the head, only sways slightly as the boss runs, 
so it should be pretty easy to target.
<BR>
Death leaves itself open the instant it starts running this way. 
If you reload before it gets started, aim upward in advance, and 
shoot as fast as you can as soon as Death starts barreling 
toward you, you should be able to stop this attack without 
taking any damage.
<img alt="Death_01.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Death_01.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
The time when you can really get some good damage in is 
<strong>the moment it swings its club up to slam you</strong>. You’ll be 
at point-blank range then, so you’ll be able to inflict maximum 
damage.
<img alt="Death_02_01.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Death_02_01.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Even if Death gets too close for comfort, try to remain calm 
and just keep getting in as many shots as you can until the 
very last second.
<BR>
<strong><u>
[2]Chases you behind columns and then wallops you.</u></strong>
When Death is running behind the columns, its head barely 
moves at all, so targeting it should be a piece of cake.
<BR>
But figuring out when to reload isn’t quite so easy. 
<strong>That’s because you’ve got to shoot when you can see 
Death between the columns, or else the columns will 
block your shots and you won’t be able to score any hits.</strong> 
If you reload after Death goes behind a column, it’ll be a tough battle. 
<BR>
<strong>The key is to start reloading before Death disappears behind 
a column, </strong>
<img alt="Death_03.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Death_03.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
<strong>and each time it appears again, get three shots in.</strong>
<img alt="Death_04.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/Death_04.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/death.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/death.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">HODIII</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 00:00:05 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>TOWER</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<img alt="BOSS3_2.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/BOSS3_2.jpg" width="260" height="347" />
Tower is a giant dragon with five heads. In order to defeat it, 
you first have to wipe out the four brown heads on the left 
and right. 
<BR>
When one of these brown heads approaches to make a 
biting attack, its mouth will glow. <strong>That’s the moment 
you should fire.</strong>
<img alt="TOWER_03_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/TOWER_03_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
Once you’ve wiped out the brown heads on the left and right, 
it’s time for one-on-one combat with the final blue head in 
the room beyond. This blue head will move around wildly and 
try to bite you. Just as with the brown heads, however, its 
mouth will glow just before it strikes, 
<img alt="TOWER_05_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/TOWER_05_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

so if you aim for its mouth and fire repeatedly, you should 
be able to defeat it without too much difficulty.
<img alt="TOWER_04_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/TOWER_04_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

<BR>
Depending on the route you took, the battleground will 
either be filled with water or sand. But despite some small 
differences in the timing of when the blue head’s mouth 
glows, the basic strategy will be the same.
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/tower.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/tower.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">HOD2</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 00:00:04 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>HIEROPHANT</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<img alt="BOSS2.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/BOSS2.jpg" width="260" height="346" />
The Hierophant is a huge aquatic zombie that wields a trident. 
Its weak point is <strong>its heart</strong>, which is covered by its thick chest. 
Bullets fired anywhere else on its body besides its heart 
will bounce away.
<BR>
The Hierophant will try to approach and attack you with 
its trident, so be sure to shoot its heart to prevent it from 
getting too close. 
<img alt="HIEROPHANT_03_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/HIEROPHANT_03_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
When the Hierophant’s health drops to nearly half, 
it’ll send zombie fish to attack you. Attempting to deal with 
all of these zombie fish would be quite difficult, 
<strong>so as soon as the Hierophant shifts into this attack, 
just concentrate on aiming for the Hierophant’s heart. </strong>
Only try to take care of the zombie fish during the intervals, 
when the Hierophant’s chest is closed.
<img alt="HIEROPHANT_04_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/HIEROPHANT_04_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
But don’t let your guard down once the zombie fish 
attacks are over! The Hierophant will now begin a jumping 
attack on you. You might be taken aback at first by the 
sudden movement,<strong> but if you aim for the Hierophant’s heart 
just as it begins to descend from the peak of a jump, </strong>
<img alt="HIEROPHANT_06_1.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/HIEROPHANT_06_1.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<strong>you should be able to bring it down.</strong>
<BR>
There are two variations of this jumping attack. 
The Hierophant will either jump up from the bridge, 
or it will jump up out of the water. If it’s jumping up 
from the bridge, its heart will be exposed just before 
it jumps, so try to get some shots in then.
<BR>
Depending on what route you took, you may face 
the Hierophant on a pier. Its attack patterns and 
the timing of its heart being exposed will be slightly 
different, but the strategy for beating it will be 
basically the same.
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/hierophant.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/hierophant.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">HOD2</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 00:00:03 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>JUDGMENT</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<img alt="BOSS1_A.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/BOSS1_A.jpg" width="260" height="347" />
Together, the headless monster Kuarl and the winged 
imp Zeal make up the Judgment boss. 
<BR>
<strong>The key is to aim for Zeal, Judgment’s weak point, 
but landing shots on Kuarl will also whittle away small 
amounts of Judgment’s health, too.</strong>
<BR>
<strong>Just as Kuarl is about to attack, Zeal will pause in its 
overhead flight. </strong>That’s the moment you’ll be able to target 
Zeal most easily. <strong>Take aim at Zeal when Kuarl grips 
its battle axe with both hands. </strong>
<img alt="JUDGMENT_01_01.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/JUDGMENT_01_01.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
Until that moment comes, however, <strong>you should make repeated 
shots at Kuarl to help wear down Judgment’s health.</strong>
<img alt="JUDGMENT_03.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/JUDGMENT_03.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<BR>
<BR>
Once you manage to reduce Judgment to thirty percent of its 
original health, a one-on-one showdown against Zeal begins. 
Zeal has two basic attack patterns.
<BR>
<strong><u>[1]Moving Left/Right or Up/Down</u></strong>
<img alt="JUDGMENT_04_01.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/JUDGMENT_04_01.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Making small movements either left and right or up and down, 
Zeal will come flying toward you. If you repeatedly fire at 
<strong>the center of its flight pattern</strong>, you should be able to 
get some shots in.
<BR>
<strong><u>
[2]Circling Left/Right</u></strong>
<img alt="JUDGMENT_05_01.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/jp/images/JUDGMENT_05_01.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
When the difficulty level is higher, Zeal will fly in a large 
circular pattern. Aim for the spot in its flight pattern 
where it makes its turn toward you, and shoot <strong>just as 
it makes its turn.</strong>
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/judgment.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/judgment.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">HOD2</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 00:00:02 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>FOREWARD</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<BR>
Welcome to the AMS.
<BR>
My name is “G.” As an AMS agent, 
I’ve been on countless missions, 
including the Curien Mansion case.
<BR>
As an AMS veteran, I thought I’d better 
write up this file for all of you rookies 
out there, to help you get through 
some of the many challenges 
I’m sure you’re going to face.
<BR>
In this file, I’m going to concentrate on 
the bosses, the enemies you newbies are 
bound to have the most trouble with, 
so pay close attention.
<BR>
But keep in mind that the boss information 
I’m going to be giving you here is classified, 
so you’d better make certain you don’t 
let any of it leak.
<BR>
Some of you might be the stubborn type, 
the kind that likes to prove you can do things 
on your own without any help. If that’s you, 
then I advise you not to look at this file.
<BR>
<strong>Remember, it’s up to you 
whether you open this file or not.</strong>
<BR>
But if you do decide to look at this information, 
make sure you learn it inside and out, backwards 
and forward, because I guarantee you you’re going 
to need it against what you’re about to face. 
Hope it helps.
<BR>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/foreward.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/HOD2and3RETURN/en/2008/03/foreward.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">FOREWORD</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 00:00:01 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
      
   </channel>
</rss>
