<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
      <title>International CES News</title>
      <link>http://www.CESweb.org</link>
      <description>Stay up-to-date on the latest developments for 2011 International CES attendees.</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 17:34:29 UTC</pubDate>
      <docs>http://www.CESweb.org/docs</docs>
      <generator>RedDot CMS 6.1.1.18</generator>
<image>
<title> </title>
<url>
<img src="http://stats.indextools.com/p.pl?a=1000217290027" />
</url>
<link>http://www.CESweb.org</link>
<width>1</width>
<height>1</height>
</image>


      <item>
         <!--/E6FBC390147042D48FBCE7000EF76F77.htm-->
         <title>Senator Tom Coburn M.D., Representative Anna Eshoo and Dr. Robert Kahn to be Honored at CEA's Digital Patriots Dinner</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4943</link> 
         <description>May 11 Digital Patriots Awards Dinner to Benefit the D.C. Opportunity Scholarship Program</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 5 Apr 2011 15:27:30 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4943</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/87F8603EFA414CACA91AFA84E74D5B71.htm-->
         <title>2011 Mark of Excellence Award Winners Announced</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4938</link> 
         <description>The Consumer Electronics Association (CEA) today announced the winners of the 2011 Mark of Excellence Awards.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 07:14:06 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4938</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/D54D2B5A6AF84F04B4A0A83715902D65.htm-->
         <title>CEA's Gary Shapiro Encourages Consumer Technology Companies to Participate in Upcoming CE Week</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4936</link> 
         <description>CEA president calls the New York event the right place and time to prepare media and trade for all-important Q4 product launches and holiday messaging.</description>
         <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2011 10:09:04 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4936</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/EDB880BCB8C14C99993F2D8C461590B2.htm-->
         <title>2012 CES iLounge Pavilion Sells Out in Record Time: Additional Space Added to Meet Demand</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4933</link> 
         <description>50,000 Square Feet of 2012 CES iLounge Exhibit Space Already Sold; Pavilion to Feature Largest Display of iPad, iPhone, iPod and Apple Products in CES History</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 17:24:08 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4933</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/77670E40B4024E6D9AB59819B0E7B68F.htm-->
         <title>2011 International CES Wows World with Innovation and Optimism</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4913</link> 
         <description>Record-breaking 30,000 overseas visitors experience world’s largest consumer technology tradeshow.</description>
         <pubDate>Sun, 9 Jan 2011 12:13:31 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4913</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/6092A0FF5FEB42F79EA2B5BA6F3AD724.htm-->
         <title>Missed A CES Keynote? Watch Them All Online </title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4896</link> 
         <description>Want to know where consumer technology is headed in 2011? Watch any or all of the 2011 CES keynote addresses.</description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 8 Jan 2011 10:19:33 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4896</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/E181D2F0A7BC495DA02F69FE1D00E9E5.htm-->
         <title>MyCES and the Online Exhibitor Directory Generate More than a Million Company Listing Views</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4879</link> 
         <description>Together, MyCES and the online exhibitor directory have generated more than a million company listing views and over 160,000 sales leads, proving their usefulness as key attendee planning tools. </description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 8 Jan 2011 07:23:05 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4879</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/EDF4F08CD13E4D54A50D8C353F447E44.htm-->
         <title>Keynotes from Ford, Cisco, GE, Xerox and the Entertainment Community Top Day Two of the 2011 CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4878</link> 
         <description>FCC Chairman Genachowski Discusses Broadband, Spectrum Reform and Competition Policy with CEA’s Shapiro</description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 8 Jan 2011 06:56:22 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4878</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/37943C27B9034420852FF087992466C6.htm-->
         <title>Microsoft Keynote and Major Product Announcements Kick Off 2011 CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4842</link> 
         <description>Ballmer keynote and pre-CES media events fuel momentum for the 2011 CES</description>
         <pubDate>Fri, 7 Jan 2011 16:57:38 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4842</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/475C8373F0014C4EA7D34BAFB1D4061D.htm-->
         <title>CEA's Gary Shapiro Available for  Book Signings On-site at CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4824</link> 
         <description></description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 6 Jan 2011 16:43:35 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4824</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/3D10A64F033742398D7A443F8FE10B57.htm-->
         <title>CEA Releases Sustainability Report, Highlights Tremendous Progress Industry has Made in Green Initiatives</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4822</link> 
         <description>The CEA 2010 Sustainability Report contains 21 separate case studies from a variety of CE companies illustrating progress in their environmental efforts. </description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 5 Jan 2011 10:28:21 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4822</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/89F1CF15844241FA86B72A3411543F9C.htm-->
         <title>Celebrities Promote Latest Consumer Technology and Trends at CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4821</link> 
         <description>Television personalities, sports icons, award winning-actors and government officials will attend the 2011 International CES to showcase and discuss the innovative products and technologies shaping consumer technology. </description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 4 Jan 2011 07:20:26 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4821</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/7A6C774318744FE6908830829751F1A5.htm-->
         <title>Huffington Post Co-founder and Editor-in-Chief Arianna Huffington Featured Speaker, Along with Netflix Keynoter Hastings, at the 2011 CES LIT Dinner</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4820</link> 
         <description>This invitation-only dinner brings top technology industry leaders and government guests together to share their experience and knowledge.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 4 Jan 2011 07:15:10 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4820</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/DDE68FAE3E114E0694720AA7F1BFE971.htm-->
         <title>Foursquare at the 2011 International CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4815</link> 
         <description></description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 09:00:04 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4815</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/F60028FF0E3641CD81F3707350CF46F3.htm-->
         <title>With a Week to Go Before CES, Exhibitors May Need These Helpful Kits and Resources</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4814</link> 
         <description>The best way to stay organized as you prep for CES is to have every resource at your fingertips. </description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 15:51:59 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4814</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/946D9DB856874D2B963C9CF28ACE862F.htm-->
         <title>Vegas Properties Offer Deep Discounts for CES Goers</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4813</link> 
         <description>Looking for a deal on a Vegas show? Want that all-you-can-eat buffet at half the price? Chek out these offers.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 15:20:11 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4813</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/818FBDACE8F5454F993E57108B37BB89.htm-->
         <title>Six Sessions to Round Out Your Four Days at CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4787</link> 
         <description>If you don't have time to attend an entire track offered in the CES Conference Program, you may want to opt for these sponsored single sessions.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 16:58:15 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4787</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/B007458C577B48039A3CA05BAC6BA41D.htm-->
         <title>New Sessions added to CES Conference Program Highlight Fitness, Cloud Computing, Smartphones and More</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4782</link> 
         <description>Take a look a these new programs brought to you by CES partners who have produced popular sessions in the past, and sign up now to save. </description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 06:20:03 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4782</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/77C1E8B02D6B4ED586809B417E347FB4.htm-->
         <title>Social Media Expands CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4781</link> 
         <description>Tradeshows are primarily about bringing people face-to-face to network and conduct business. Social networking tools can help make this happen by better connecting people. </description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 06:04:51 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4781</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/152228D120C44DDEBE29C1C92698FF20.htm-->
         <title>Making the Home Connection</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4780</link> 
         <description>By Sue Schreiner from the November/December 2010 issue of Vision Magazine</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 17:57:46 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4780</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/6A1A388BF8E641849925ED4C5AD35813.htm-->
         <title>Team LightBulb, Clasma Events and Parnassus to Produce New Sessions for 2011 CES Conference Program</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4744</link> 
         <description>Making last-minute decisions on your 2011 CES schedule? Consider these conference program tracks from new partners! </description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 16:18:58 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4744</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/8F70303BA59448CFB67C80F038E1AE13.htm-->
         <title>Pre-order Now Available for The Comeback: How Innovation will Restore the American Dream</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4585</link> 
         <description>In The Comeback, Gary Shapiro shows us how to return innovation to its rightful place at the center of America’s economic policy. The Comeback is a new blueprint for America’s success.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 15:48:29 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4585</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/98A13A87ABDB44BFA74A46D0FC40C194.htm-->
         <title>Broadband Communications – New Ways to Relieve Capacity Woes</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4584</link> 
         <description>Broadband communications capabilities are increasingly stressed by the demand for high-bandwidth applications such as video, videoconferencing, telemedicine and cloud computing.</description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 08:27:56 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4584</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/CA304D376F9645D5BB0F77E652932C09.htm-->
         <title>Boomers Boost Your Bottom Line</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4583</link> 
         <description>There are about 78 million boomers in the US (450 million worldwide) born between 1946 and 1964 — and they're hitting their peak earning and spending.</description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 08:24:58 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4583</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/5B18EBCF017F4386A3A8F062836F216D.htm-->
         <title>Media Money Makers: Turn Content Into Cash</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4582</link> 
         <description>Media Money Makers, co-sponsored by The Nielsen Co., cuts through the technobabble to reveal reliable business models for monetizing content across the most promising platforms. </description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 08:21:13 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4582</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/85C46E22270E4D8E896480B6610E8A96.htm-->
         <title>CEA Launches Tech Enthusiast Membership for Individuals </title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4529</link> 
         <description>For the first time in its 86-year history, the Consumer Electronics Association (CEA) has created a membership category exclusively for individuals who are early adopters and fervent supporters of consumer technology. </description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 9 Nov 2010 17:36:53 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4529</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/ECC2153974C34E1AA7F087B527512CD7.htm-->
         <title>On-air Promotional Opportunities at CES with Dave Graveline</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4523</link> 
         <description>Covering the latest in consumer electronics, "Into Tomorrow with Dave Graveline" will launch their 16th year at the International CES in January. </description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 3 Nov 2010 08:42:22 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4523</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/EF68F35EE4224B0A8243B14DBEB4D9C9.htm-->
         <title>Mashable Awards Come to CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4510</link> 
         <description>Mashable is proud to present the fourth annual Mashable Awards, which celebrates major innovations and achievements in the digital and social media landscape.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 16:49:38 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4510</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/07567EBA73BA412EBC1EF07E00D40F1A.htm-->
         <title>The National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences Announced Recipients of 62nd Annual Technology and Engineering  Emmy Awards to Take Place at CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4489</link> 
         <description>The National Academy’s prestigious Lifetime Achievement Award in Technology and Engineering will be presented to Sir Howard Stringer, Chairman and CEO of Sony Corporation. </description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 15:08:17 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4489</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/5BDCB54D314C4896A799A81BD695B958.htm-->
         <title>Living in Digital Times Announced Keynote Speakers for Lifestyle Tracks at 2011 CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#4450</link> 
         <description>The lifestyle conference tracks taking place at the 2011 CES focus on the fastest-growing technology consumer markets – from parents and children, to students, young adults, and seniors. </description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 15:25:55 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">4450</guid>
      </item>

</channel>
</rss>
