<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>Himiring-Do（Ring Guide)</title>
      <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/</link>
      <description>Contains collection of gameplay hints for &apos;Sonic and the Secret Rings&apos; (Wii).Aim to become the grand master of Himiring-Do!</description>
      <language>ja</language>
      <copyright>Copyright 2007</copyright>
      <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 May 2007 05:12:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
      <generator>http://www.sixapart.com/movabletype/</generator>
      <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs> 

            <item>
         <title>Fire Soul Strategies  -Correction notice-</title>
         <description><![CDATA[You can collect Fire Souls during the missions to unlock mini-games in Party Mode as well as hidden characters. You can find some just by playing normally, but there are some that are more difficult to collect. Below is a summary of some of the more hard-to-find Fire Souls.




<strong class="txt-large">Sand Oasis (Find King Shahryar)</strong>
For the first Fire Soul: When you press the switch pad underneath the  iron ball, pillars will appear. They are too high to reach with a normal jump, however, so it’s very difficult to get the Fire Soul without the Splash Jump skill. If you have Splash Jump equipped, do a jump attack toward the pillar to easily grab the Fire Soul.
(Difficulty: medium)

<img alt="screenshot_0003.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0003.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0011.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0011.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Sand Oasis (Don’t break the jar)</strong>
For the first Fire Soul (near the exit back to the outside): The Fire Soul is right above a jar near the middle of the slope. You need to jump to grab it, but the timing is a bit tricky, and hitting the jar will result in mission failure. 
While it depends on your speed, it may be easier to grab the ring if you jump from a position relatively close to the jar.
(Difficulty: medium)

<img alt="screenshot_0013.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0013.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Sand Oasis (Break 5 jars)</strong>
For the second Fire Soul (second lap): The Fire Soul is positioned near spike traps, and it may be difficult to grab it without being damaged by the spikes. Using Time Break or Speed Break will make it easier to pick up.
(Difficulty: medium)

<img alt="screenshot_0018.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0018.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Dinosaur Jungle (Follow the Pterosaur)</strong>
For the first Fire Soul (in a cage): You will need to use trampolines to jump higher, but if Sonic’s position is even a little bit off when you do the Homing Attacks, you won’t be able to lock on to the trampolines. You will need to adjust Sonic’s position each time, making this sequence difficult. You can jump higher if you do the Homing Attack at the top of your jump, so try gaining height to give yourself time to adjust.
(Difficulty: high)

<img alt="screenshot_0024.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0024.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

For the second Fire Soul (on the shortcut accessed via the catapult): You need to defeat three Enemies so you can use the catapult, but after you defeat the Enemies, you will need to stop and gauge the right timing to use the catapult. Unless you wait, it’s easy to pass by without even noticing what you need to do. After you defeat the three Enemies, wait, and charge your Charge Jump until the catapult appears.
(Difficult: medium)

<img alt="screenshot_0026.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0026.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0027.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0027.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Dinosaur Jungle (Defeat 10 Enemies)</strong>
For the second Fire Soul (on the route where you don’t use the Jump Pad): It may be difficult to notice that you need to need to avoid using the Jump Pad and use jump + Jump Dash in order to access this hidden route.
It looks like a speed board, so many players will simply hop on, but it’s important to jump over it instead.
(Difficulty: high)

<img alt="screenshot_0035.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0035.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0037.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0037.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Dinosaur Jungle (Don’t defeat enemies)</strong>
For the first Fire Soul (on the route where you don’t use the Air Launcher): When you hop into the first Air Launcher in the mission, wait until the Rings go through a “large  small  large” cycle, then flick the Wii Remote at “large” to go straight to the dinosaur’s head without using the next Air Launcher. This can be difficult to figure out.
The key here is to determine the size of the Air Launcher, and figure out the right strength so you don’t enter the next Air Launcher.
(Difficulty: medium)

<img alt="screenshot_0039.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0039.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0041.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0041.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Levitated Ruin (Find Sinbad)</strong>
For the <del>second</del> third Fire Soul (placed on a grind): You can pick up the Fire Soul simply by grinding, so that part is easy, but it’s very difficult to avoid taking damage from the obstacles after you collect it. Use Time Break to increase your chances of avoiding damage.
(Difficulty: medium)

<img alt="screenshot_0044.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0044.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0048.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0048.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Pirate Storm (Follow the Pirates)</strong>
For the second Fire Soul (above a  iron ball on a grind rail): To get to the area where the Fire Soul is located, you will need to jump when the catapult is half-cocked, so it may be difficult to figure out.
Once you’re on the grind rail, charge your jump and Jump Dash at the right timing. This can be very difficult, though—tilting the Wii Remote during the grind can send you jumping in the wrong direction, and unless it’s a small jump you’ll pass right through. But if you jump too low, you’ll hit the  iron ball. If you get the hang of the catapult power level and start your Charge Jump as soon as you start grinding, you’ll have a little more time to make sure you get the controls right.
(Difficulty: high)

<img alt="screenshot_0052.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0052.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0058.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0058.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Skeleton Dome (Find King Solomon)</strong>
For the third Fire Soul: Take advantage of enemies to get up to the area where the treasure chest is, and use a Time Break near the treasure chest to slow the rotation of the rolling spiked balls ahead. You can then use the Spring to jump. In the cage beyond is a Fire Soul that you can pick up when in Time Break.
Since you will need to use Time Break heavily to get this Fire Soul, make sure to build up energy in the Soul Gauge.
(Difficulty: medium)

<img alt="screenshot_0063.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0063.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0066.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0066.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Night Palace (Sneak into the palace)</strong>
For the second and third Fire Souls: Both Fire Souls are difficult to get without equipping Slowed Search and using Time Break.
In both cases, you need to use Time Break before the columns are restored, so make sure you build up enough energy in the Soul Gauge beforehand.
The Fire Souls are positioned relatively high up, so the key is to do Homing Attacks on the same obstacles that you can lock on to.
(Difficulty: high)

<img alt="screenshot_0067.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0067.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0069.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0069.jpg" width="260" height="195" />]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/05/fire_soul_strategies.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/05/fire_soul_strategies.html</guid>
        
        
         <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2007 05:12:04 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>At the end NEW</title>
         <description><![CDATA[This is the end of the Himiring-Do!

We hope this information was useful for everyone who have already bought Sonic and the Secret Rings, or even for the people who are planning to start playing the game.

Sonic and the Secret Rings is a challenging game for the Wii.

It is like riding a bicycle without using the safety wheel.

Some people may even have quit playing the game.

However, please remember that the road to freedom is still waiting for you right around the corner.

When you finally manage to freely control Sonic with the Wii remote, You will experience the fun of "controlling the fastest sense of speed".

I even feel that this may be the true aspect of the new generation games.

The road to the true Sonic and the Secret Rings experience has just begun!
<strong>You can also become the Sonic and the Secret Rings master!</strong>
]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/to_the_end.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/to_the_end.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Tactics</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2007 09:33:33 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Try Playing with One Hand! NEW</title>
         <description><![CDATA[For players who have cleared all of the missions, leveled up to the highest level, collected all of the Gold Medals and have pretty much seen everything there is to see in the game, we recommend trying to play the game with one hand.
Take advantage of the Wii Remote’s unique abilities to master the ultimate playing style for Sonic and the Secret Rings!
Details and notes are summarized below, so please use them as reference.




Holding: Hold the Wii Remote sideways with both hands.
<img alt="hand_000.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/hand_000.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




Tilting: Hold the Wii Remote sideways with both hands.
<img alt="hand_002.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/hand_002.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="hand_005.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/hand_005.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




You use both hands except when swinging, when you switch to one hand. 




Swing 1: Let go with the left hand, and use the right hand to tilt the Wii Remote to the right momentarily, then swing down to the left.
<img alt="hand_007.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/hand_007.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<img alt="hand_011.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/hand_011.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<img alt="hand_012.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/hand_012.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




Swing 2: Swing with one hand as in Swing 1. Swing the Wii Remote tapping it against the left palm.
<img alt="hand_015.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/hand_015.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<img alt="hand_016.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/hand_016.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<img alt="hand_018.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/hand_018.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<img alt="screenshot_058.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/images/screenshot_058.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
For scenes where you need to continuously swing the remote, "Swing 1" would be the best way to swing.




<img alt="screenshot_108.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/images/screenshot_108.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="hand_015.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/hand_015.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
When input timing is severe, use "Swing 2" by narrowing the width of the swinging range.
  For example, at scenes like the left image wait for the red lock-on mark to appear
  As shown in the right image.


Use the one-hand-style and try the cool play style out!
]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/try_playing_with_one_hand.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/try_playing_with_one_hand.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Tactics</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2007 01:03:12 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Master the Ultimate Jump</title>
         <description><![CDATA[Perhaps you’ve noticed Sonic occasionally do an amazing jump when he hits an obstacle during gameplay.
In Sonic and the Secret Rings, Sonic’s actions are governed by physics calculations, so depending on Sonic’s speed and the angle at which he hits an obstacle, he can perform jumps beyond his usual abilities.
The controls are very difficult if you try to do this on purpose, and it’s nearly impossible to perform consistently.
The trick is to jump so you glance off the corner of an obstacle. If you can pull this off, you can skip nasty traps and save time. The timing of the jump is affected by the shape of the obstacle, but it’s a useful trick for advanced players.
Once you master this jump, you can use it to blaze your own trails through the missions.




<strong class="txt-large">Super Play</strong>
<strong>NIGHT PALACE
Beat the Clock "Finish within 90 seconds!!"</strong>
<object width="425" height="350"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/JR7PfRyH5gA"></param><param name="wmode" value="transparent"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/JR7PfRyH5gA" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" wmode="transparent" width="425" height="350"></embed></object>
Create a great speed-up by crashing into the fallen column.
This will allow you to do a jump you usually cannot do.

]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/master_the_ultimate_jump.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/master_the_ultimate_jump.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Tactics</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2007 01:11:29 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Going for the Gold part3</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<strong class="txt-large">“Finish within X seconds” missions</strong>
Like the “beat Uhu to the goal” missions, this is a pure test of speed.
For missions with time limits, if you proceed along the normal route you will generally make it to the goal just in time. But if you explore and look for other routes, you may find gimmicks and hidden courses that offer shortcuts in unexpected places.
<img alt="screenshot_0037b.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0037b.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0042b.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0042b.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">“Don’t get any Pearls” missions</strong>
These missions require very precise controls, as you will fail if you pick up even one Pearl.
Pearl Collector-type skills are obviously not a good idea in this case, so make sure to remove them. While precise controls are required, this is also a race against the clock, so you will need to learn where the Pearls are, and dash through the course as quickly as possible.
The Pearls are often placed in lines, so they may make it easier to see the course you need to follow in order to avoid them. But in later stages, the courses add more vertical dimensions so you need to use Short Jumps to avoid Pearls. You may simply need to play the stages multiple times to get the hang of it.
<img alt="screenshot_0051.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0051.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0055.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0055.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">“Don’t take damage” missions</strong>
Even simply clearing the mission is difficult, since you fail if you take damage even once. Given that you need to do this at high speeds to get a time good enough for a Gold Medal, the difficulty level is even higher.
You will need to learn the courses, as well as use all of the gameplay skills you’ve learned so far. Equipping Aegis Slider to avoid damage from sneaky traps should help.
<img alt="screenshot_0056a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0056a.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0058a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0058a.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">“ Finish with 0 Rings” missions</strong>
Picking up a Ring will not automatically cause you to fail the mission—as long as you have no Rings when you reach the goal, you can clear the mission. It may seem that it might be faster to collect Rings as you go, then take damage on purpose to drop the Rings before the goal line. But this approach adds the risk of choosing the wrong place to take damage, and taking damage takes time as well. It’s best if you can clear the mission without picking up Rings.
Similar to the “Don’t get any Pearls” missions, learning the location of the Rings is key. But if you find it too difficult to get to the end without picking up any Rings, you can make things easier for yourself by equipping Ring Exchange, and you can focus only on enemies and obstacles without worrying about Rings for an easy Gold Medal.
<img alt="screenshot_0065a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0065a.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0059a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0059a.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">“Get an X-Ring chain” missions</strong>
Due to its similarity to the “collect Rings” missions, it may seem like the Ring Bonus skill would be useful, but since the mission counts Ring Chains instead of the total number of Rings you have, Ring Bonus won’t help you clear the mission.
As noted in the Advanced Strategies section, tactics such as using Speed Break to grab large numbers of Rings at once or using Time Break to slow down time and make sure you don’t miss any Rings are effective.
Also, Platinum Rings appear in these Ring Chain missions as well, but they only count as one Ring instead of 20, so there is no reason to go out of your way to get them.
Find routes that allow you to maintain an unbroken chain, and remember to slow down right before you reach the required number of Rings so the chain will end.
<img alt="screenshot_0071a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0071a.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0075a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0075a.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Super Play</strong>
<strong>SKELETON DOME
No Pearl "Don't get any Pearls!"</strong>
<object width="425" height="350"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/_sNwckWbJJI"></param><param name="wmode" value="transparent"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/_sNwckWbJJI" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" wmode="transparent" width="425" height="350"></embed></object>
This has been completed using the route leading to the left which is right after the starting point.




<strong>NIGHT PALACE
Perfect Challenge "Don't take damage!"</strong>
<object width="425" height="350"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/0v-X9-QCrXE"></param><param name="wmode" value="transparent"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/0v-X9-QCrXE" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" wmode="transparent" width="425" height="350"></embed></object>
When you come to the stair like steps in the latter part of the rotating room, do a small jump towards the cylindrical column to jump over all of the steps.
]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/going_for_the_gold_part3_new.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/going_for_the_gold_part3_new.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Tactics</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2007 04:51:05 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Going for the Gold part2</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<strong class="txt-large">Effective Skills for Gold Medals by Mission Type</strong>
Below is a summary of effective skills and tips for each of the common mission types.




<strong class="txt-large">“Defeat Enemies” missions</strong>
The key is to defeat enemies as quickly as possible.
Equipping attack-type skills like Fire Gaze, Fire Tackle and Volcano Slider is good, but focusing on upgrading the Homing Attack with skills like Rocket Jump, H-Mega Expand and Homing Recovery may be more helpful in cutting your time.
<img alt="screenshot_0014.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0014.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0015.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0015.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">“Don’t defeat enemies” missions</strong>
Defeating an enemy will result in immediate failure, so avoid any attack-type skills. Instead, consider Aegis Slider so you can get by enemies without taking damage or losing time.
Also, since there’s no need to lock on to enemies, you don’t need any H Expand-type skills. And if you start a Homing Attack by mistake, use Homing Cancel.
Learn enemy positions, and figure out a route that will allow you to avoid them most efficiently.
<img alt="screenshot_0022.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0022.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0023.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0023.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">“Don’t get defeated” missions</strong>
Simply taking damage won’t result in failure, so clearing the mission shouldn’t be too difficult. Taking damage takes up time, though, so you will need to play like the “don’t defeat enemies” and “don’t take damage” missions.
In these missions, of course, you can defeat enemies, so in some cases you can get a better overall time by spending some time to defeat enemies and collect Pearls.
As far as skills go, you can do fairly well with the recommended skills above.
<img alt="screenshot_0024b.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0024b.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0025b.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0025b.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">“Collect Rings” missions</strong>
As mentioned earlier, equipping Ring Bonus to start the mission with Rings is almost a requirement to get a better time.
Making sure you don’t miss any Rings is a no-brainer, but in some cases, it may be faster to go out of your way to pick up Rich Rings (worth 20 Rings), so learn where they are.
<img alt="screenshot_0026b.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0026b.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0028b.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0028b.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">“Beat Uhu to the goal” missions</strong>
Since you need to beat Uhu by a wide margin to earn the Gold Medal, you don’t need to worry about Uhu too much. Instead, equip the recommended skills and use Speed Break effectively on the straight-aways to get a shorter time.
The number on the upper right shows the distance between Sonic and the Uhu. When playing this mission repeatedly, you can use this number to give you an idea of your time.
<img alt="screenshot_0029b.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0029b.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0034b.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0034b.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Super Play</strong>
<strong>SKELETON DOME
Rampage! "Defeat 40 Genies!"</strong>
<object width="425" height="350"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/BljIY7Rtjr0"></param><param name="wmode" value="transparent"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/BljIY7Rtjr0" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" wmode="transparent" width="425" height="350"></embed></object>
Try delaying the swinging timing of the controller by consecutively doing a homing attack.
  Then, defeat the enemies by first locking-on the enemies in the close range in the outer part of the screen and then defeat the enemies in the farther distance.
]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/going_for_the_gold_part2.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/going_for_the_gold_part2.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Tactics</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2007 04:33:13 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Going for the Gold part1</title>
         <description><![CDATA[Gold Medals help you unlock items in the Special Book as well as certain skills.
You need to clear missions within a certain time to earn Gold Medals, so speed becomes key. The information below describes how to customize Sonic for speed, as well as tips for each mission type.
<br />
<strong class="txt-large">Recommended Skills</strong>
Charger, All-Rounder, Quick High Step, Super Quick Air, Warp Boost, Super Speed-Up, Landing Boost, Cancel Boost, Splash Jump, Rocket Jump, H-Mega Expand, Homing Recovery, Quick Jump, Warp Dash
Default skills (8)

<strong>Skill point total: 288 (363 including defaults)</strong>
<strong>Equippable level for skills: Level 57 – 66</strong>
<br />
If you do not yet have enough skill points or levels, you can adjust by using less powerful versions of the skills listed above.
]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/going_for_the_gold_part1.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/going_for_the_gold_part1.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Tactics</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2007 05:30:19 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Explaining Selected Skills</title>
         <description><![CDATA[There are many skills in this game, but there are some that can be used in unique ways, have unique effects, or can become even more useful when combined with other skills.




<strong class="txt-large">Aegis Slider</strong>
This skill adds defensive power while sliding, and is the only skill that allows you to avoid taking damage from traps. You can be hit by spikes or flames coming from the ground as well as   iron balls without taking damage.
This applies only when you are sliding, so you can combine this skill with the sliding-type skills mentioned below for even more effectiveness.
While this is a useful skill, you can take damage when you come to a complete stop after sliding, so you still need to be careful.
<img alt="screenshot_0064.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0064.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0066a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0066a.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Splash Jump</strong>
This skill allows you to jump even higher by hitting an obstacle while jumping, similar to a double jump.
It’s a relatively high-level skill that also consumes a lot of skill points, but it’s useful in enough situations to make it worth the cost.
This skill can be used from a Short Jump as well, so you can use it without trying too hard. It really shines, however, when climbing to high places or getting over walls that you needed to use enemies to clear. Once you get the hang of it, it can be useful in finding new paths to follow.
Note, though, that Splash Jump won’t work with the black rock obstacles that break when you defeat certain enemies.
<img alt="screenshot_0075.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0075.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0076.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0076.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Ring Exchange</strong>
This skill adds energy to the Soul Gauge when you collect Rings, and is useful for players who want to use Speed Break and Time Break aggressively.
With this skill, you can use Speed Break and Time Break for long periods of time on missions with large number of Pearls or Rings. Keep in mind, however, that picking up more Rings won’t increase the number of Rings you have, so you run a greater risk of defeat when you take damage.
Also, on “Collect X Rings” missions, since collecting Rings won’t increase your Ring count, you may be unable to clear the mission at all. You may also become unable to get past the Poisonous mist area on the long mission in Night Palace, so in cases like these, make sure to remove the skill beforehand.
Or, you can take advantage of this skill on missions like “Reach the goal with 0 Rings” to run through without worrying about picking up Rings.
<img alt="screenshot_0024a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0024a.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Slowed Search</strong>
At first glance, you may not notice much difference when you equip this skill, and there are few opportunities to use it.
There are times when it’s very useful, however—it allows you to do Homing Attacks on the Ifrit Golem’s gas tanks to hit them back and damage the boss. Also, you can do Homing Attacks on the columns that the wind blows toward you in Levitated Ruins, and the columns that get restored in Night Palace. For the columns in Night Palace in particular, you’ll need to use them to get Fire Souls, so it’s worth your while to equip this skill.
You won’t need to spend many skill points to get this skill, so if you use Time Breaks often, it’s a good skill to have.
<img alt="screenshot_0094.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0094.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0095.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0095.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Skill Combinations</strong>
The combinations below are some of the useful pairings that involve special skills. Try different combinations to see what works for your playing style.




<strong class="txt-large">Ring of Zero + Ring Exchange + an Experience Point-type skill</strong>
The effects of Ring Exchange will prevent your Ring count from increasing, making it easier to maintain the effects from Ring of Zero.
Since Ring of Zero acts to amplify experience-related skills, equipping a skill that matches your playing style should help you earn large amounts of Experience Points.
Keep in mind, however, that since you cannot gain Rings, you run a much higher risk when taking damage. Also, make sure you don’t have Ring Bonus equipped, since that will give you Rings at the start of the mission.
<img alt="screenshot_0026a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0026a.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0027a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0027a.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Skimmer-type skill + Quick Slide-type skill + Aegis Slider or Volcano Slider</strong>
Aegis Slider and Volcano Slider are very powerful skills, but they are effective only while Sonic is sliding. To make them easier to use in more situations, combine them with a Skimmer-type skill and a Quick Slide-type skill to allow you to slide longer, and with more control.
Learn the Sliding Cancel discussed in the Advanced Strategies section to avoid dangerous traps.
<img alt="screenshot_0036.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0036.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0037a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0037a.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Sub C-Devour + Soul Barrier</strong>
By using up the Rings you’ve collected with Sub C-Devour, you can use the effects of Soul Barrier to build up energy in the Soul Gauge.
This is difficult if there aren’t a lot of Rings in the mission, but it’s an effective combination if you want to charge your Soul Gauge quickly.
<img alt="screenshot_0042.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0042.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0043.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0043.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Super Play</strong>
<strong>LEVITATED RUIN
Go for the Goal　"Find Sinbad!"</strong>
<object width="425" height="350"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/2pscQaxDoAc"></param><param name="wmode" value="transparent"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/2pscQaxDoAc" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" wmode="transparent" width="425" height="350"></embed></object>
  There are a lot of sections you can use Speed Brake, so upgrade the soul gage using Ring Excvhange.
  Use Skimmer type + Quick Slide type + Volcano Slider skills for enemies that suddenly appear since you are in full speed.

]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/explaining_selected_skills_1.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/explaining_selected_skills_1.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Tactics</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2007 05:23:37 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Wall Shuffle Techniques</title>
         <description><![CDATA[In areas where Sonic must move along narrow ledges with his back to the wall, you can wall shuffle by tilting the Wii Remote to the left or right. Perhaps you’ve noticed that even if you equip a Speed Up-type skill, Sonic doesn’t shuffle much faster.
Actually, Sonic’s wall shuffling speed is affected by Quick Step-type skills, and if you equip Quick Mega Step, you should experience a real boost in speed. The extra speed will make controlling Sonic that much more difficult, so be careful.

Here are some tips regarding wall shuffling:
Before you begin shuffling along the wall, jump in using Short Jump or Charge Jump, and before Sonic lands, do a Jump Dash to proceed without wall shuffling. This is risky in areas with spikes or  iron balls, but it’s an effective option in areas with few obstacles.

<img alt="screenshot_0046.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0046.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0047.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0047.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

Alternatively, you can equip the Aegis Slider skill and a Skimmer-type skill and slide at top speed before Sonic starts shuffling along the wall. This allows you to slide through the entire wall area, with relatively low risk of taking damage. If wall shuffling isn’t your thing, it may be worth giving this tactic a try.

<img alt="screenshot_0057.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0057.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0059.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0059.jpg" width="260" height="195" />




<strong class="txt-large">Super Play</strong>
<strong>EVIL FOUNDRY
Go for the Goal　"Head for the Center!"</strong>
<object width="425" height="350"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/1LYTKKasX1c"></param><param name="wmode" value="transparent"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/1LYTKKasX1c" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" wmode="transparent" width="425" height="350"></embed></object>
Use "Aegis Slider" and "Hyper Skimmer" to breakthrough the wall scene located at the first phase of the stage.

]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/wall_shuffle_techniques.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/wall_shuffle_techniques.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Tactics</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2007 05:19:43 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Boss Strategies(NOTE! We have completed up to the later bosses!!)</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<strong class="txt-large">Sand Scorpion</strong>

<img alt="screenshot_57.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_57.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

A scorpion boss that appears in Sand Oasis.
If you run up to the Sand Scorpion, it will attack you with its tail. You can inflict damage by launching a Homing Attack on the eye on its tail, then work your way up to the eye on its back. If you’re not quick enough it will begin dropping missiles on you, so try to make your approach quickly without losing speed.
The Sand Scorpion also has a stabbing attack that doesn’t give you a big opening, but if you use Time Break you can do a Homing Attack on the eye on its tail. If you have extra energy in the Soul Gauge, this tactic can be useful.

<img alt="screenshot_84.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_84.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

When you do enough damage to the eye on its back, the second phase begins. The Sand Scorpion will attack with its huge fangs, so evade it and counterattack when the jaws are on their way back. The jaws return fairly quickly, so you can damage the boss more easily if you have a Turbo Jump-type skill equipped. If it still seems difficult, you can use Time Break to make it easier. Not too many Pearls appear in the mission, however, so you will need to plan carefully.

<img alt="screenshot_78.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_78.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<br />
<br />
<strong class="txt-large">Captain Bemoth</strong>

<img alt="screenshot_0119.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0119.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

The combined form of the Slime DjinnEnemies that appear in Pirate Storm.
When you get close enough to Captain Bemoth, you can jump and do a Homing Attack on the captain’s horns. If the Homing Attack succeeds, Sonic will grab onto a horn. You can then waggle the Wii Remote to pull it out. While you’re pulling out the horn, Captain Bemoth will build up an electric charge, so if a lightning attack comes your way press the 2 Button to let go of the horn and evade the attack.
After Sonic pulls out a horn, Captain Bemoth will face front and launch his tidal wave attack. The waves will go in the direction he swings his arms, so watch his movements carefully and evade his attacks. After two attacks to the left or right the third attack will always be a two-handed tidal wave, so it’s good to start a Charge Jump during his wind-up. If you have Aegis Slider equipped, you can use it to evade the tidal wave, so it’s a safer option for players who have trouble evading to the sides.

<img alt="screenshot_0118.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0118.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0125.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0125.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

In addition, you can use Speed Break to charge the captain (except during tidal wave attacks and speed board jumps). If the Speed Break hits, the captain will be knocked unconscious, so it will be easier to do Homing Attacks on the horns.
<br />
<br />
<strong class="txt-large">Ifrit Golem</strong>

<img alt="screenshot_0102a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0102a.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

A robot-like boss that appears in Evil Foundry.
The point of view switches to a side view, and the controls may take some getting used to, but the basics are still the same. Start off by attacking the three weak points on the Ifrit’s fists.
Destroying the three points knocks the boss off balance, so launch Homing Attacks on the floating tanks to avoid the magma, and then work your way up his arm and back to his head, and do Homing Attacks on the weak point on the head.
You can then repeat these steps, but after you do a certain amount of damage, the Ifrit will sink into the magma and attack with gas tanks. When this happens, if you equip Slowed Search and use a Time Break, you can lock on to the thrown gas tanks. Doing Homing Attacks on the gas tanks will send them flying back at the Ifrit Golem for damage.
Also, using a Speed Break when the Ifrit is off balance allows you to run across the magma. Continue running to do damage to the Ifrit’s head.
You can use the two types of breaks to find the tactics that work best for you.

<img alt="screenshot_0112.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0112.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0109a.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0109a.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<br />
<br />
<strong class="txt-large">Erazor Djinn</strong>

<img alt="screenshot_0101.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0101.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

The boss of Night Palace, and the cause of all of the troubles in the worlds of the Arabian Nights.
He has a wide variety of weapon attacks, which don’t leave many openings for you to counterattack. There are some, though—avoid the Z and L-shaped slashes with a Charge Jump, and launch Homing Attacks.
After a while, a side-view battle begins. Once in this mode, you can launch Homing Attacks at the right timing to inflict large amounts of damage. Using Time Breaks will make these Homing Attacks much easier.

<img alt="screenshot_0107.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0107.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_0110.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0110.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

After you do a certain amount of damage to Erazor Djinn, there is a maximum of three pattern changes. As he enters a new phase, his attacks will become faster, and more difficult to avoid. But even with faster attacks, it should still be possible to avoid them if you recognize the attack patterns below.
The letters V, L, I and Z indicate weapon attack patterns, and “side view” indicates a transition to side view mode.

<img alt="screenshot_0104.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_0104.jpg" width="260" height="195" />

<strong>Phase 1</strong>
V --> I --> L --> I --> I --> side view --> I --> back to beginning

<strong>Phase 2</strong>
I --> L --> I --> V --> I --> Z --> I --> side view --> back to beginning

<strong>Phase 3</strong>
I --> V --> I --> Z --> I --> I --> V --> L --> V --> V --> Z --> side view --> back to beginning
<br />
<br />
<strong class="txt-large">Super Play</strong>
<strong>EVIL FOUNDRY
Defeat the Boss "Battle! Golem!"</strong>
<object width="425" height="350"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/b9GEX4ROYZE"></param><param name="wmode" value="transparent"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/b9GEX4ROYZE" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" wmode="transparent" width="425" height="350"></embed></object>
Use Speed Brake to damage the weak point on the head for tactics.

]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/boss_strategies.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/boss_strategies.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Tactics</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 04:54:14 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Enemy Strategies</title>
         <description><![CDATA[Many Enemies await Sonic as he makes his way through the stages. Many can be defeated easily using the Homing Attack, but here are some strategies for dealing with some of the more troublesome Enemies and bosses.
<br />
<br />
<strong class="txt-large">Rafflesia Djinn</strong>
These enemies appear in Dinosaur Jungle, and can be difficult to deal with—they can take a lot of damage, and cannot be damaged when the petals are closed.
You can defeat a 　Rafflesia Djinn with three Homing Attacks, but delaying your timing slightly on the second and third attacks will make the Homing Attacks slightly easier. If you take too much time, though, it shoots at you, so use the Homing Attack on the projectiles to avoid taking damage.
It will close its petals to defend itself, but continue using Homing Attacks to break through its defense. Also, like with any other tough enemy, Fire Gaze is useful in defeating it quickly.

<img alt="screenshot_07.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_07.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_13.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_13.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<br />
<br />
<strong class="txt-large">Gargoyle Djinn</strong>
Gargoyle Djinns are powerful enemies that have a variety of attacks, including petrification. It can take a lot of damage, and if you don’t defeat it quickly it can turn you to stone and follow up by swiping at you with its claws.
While powerful, a  Gargoyle Djinn takes time to appear, and there is a delay before it starts attacking. Accurately predicting the spot where it will appear and getting the first attack in will make things easier. Once you land the first attack, draw it in slightly for a second and third Homing Attack, as in the case of the 　Rafflesia Djinn. If you follow up too quickly, the lock-on may fail, or you may attack during the previous hit animation, preventing you from doing damage efficiently.

<img alt="screenshot_19.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_19.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_36.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_36.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<br />
<br />
<strong class="txt-large">Slime Djinn</strong>
The Slime Djinn can be defeated with relative ease, but it turns into a challenge in missions where you need to finish without taking any damage. While it is less of a problem alone, it becomes much more difficult to deal with in groups.
Ideally, you can defeat it quickly using a Homing Stability-type skill. But if not, be careful to watch your timing in using Homing Attacks. If you land a Homing Attack when a Slime Djinn is electrified, you’ll take damage, so watch out. But if you find yourself starting a Homing Attack on an electrified Slime Djinn, you can cancel the Homing Attack to avoid the nasty shock.

<img alt="screenshot_38.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_38.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_41.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_41.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
<br />
<br />
<strong class="txt-large">Skeleton Djinn</strong>
A skeleton enemy that appears in the Skeleton Dome. It cannot withstand too many hits, but it attacks frequently, and its double-armed sword spinning attack has a longer range than it looks. If you use a Speed Break during its spinning attack you may end up taking damage, so caution is required.
Homing Attacks are your best bet, but a low Homing Attack can also be stopped by the Skeleton Djinn’s spinning attack, so be careful.

Every once in a while, you will encounter a Skeleton Djinn that comes back to life after it is defeated. It will continue to do this no matter how many times you defeat it, so ignore it and move on. These reviving Skeleton DjinnEnemies are not counted as part of the enemies you defeat, so you can ignore them in missions where you are trying to defeat a set number of enemies.

<img alt="screenshot_49.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_49.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_55.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_55.jpg" width="260" height="195" />]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/enemy_strategies.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/04/enemy_strategies.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Tactics</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 04:41:57 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Useful skills for maximizing Experience Points</title>
         <description><![CDATA[There are some skills that allow you to earn Experience Points during missions by fulfilling certain conditions. Most of these, however, are powerful skills that are relatively difficult to obtain.
Experience Points earned in this manner are shown in the Experience Bonus section of the results screen.




<strong class="txt-large">Expert Attack</strong>
You can obtain this skill by getting the Gold Medal on Pirate Storm: Die Hard Challenge.
You will earn Experience Points each time you do a Homing Attack.
This skill gives you Experience Points for using a move you use frequently anyway, so you can earn Experience without even trying.




<strong class="txt-large">Expert Drift</strong>
You can obtain this skill by getting the Gold Medal on Pirate Storm: No Pearls.
You will earn Experience Points each time you drift around a corner.
You don’t need to use any special controls to drift, but you need to have enough speed as you approach the corner. Not too many stages have sharp corners, but those that do have a lot of them, making this skill very useful on those stages.
<img alt="screenshot_104x.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_104x.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_106.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_106.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
If you press and hold the 2 Button while drifting, you can jump immediately after the drift. This will allow you to avoid any traps that lurk right after a sharp corner without having to brake.




<strong class="txt-large">Homing Bonus</strong>
You can obtain this skill by getting the Gold Medal on Night Palace: Head to Head.
You will earn Experience Points each time you defeat multiple Enemies with Homing Attacks.
Unlike with Expert Attack you will need to defeat Enemies, but you will be rewarded with even more Experience Points. This is a great skill to use in places with large, concentrated groups of enemies.
<img alt="screenshot_112.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_112.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Chains will be reset if you land, slide, or jump in between.
Even if you do a homing attack at springs or treasure boxes the chains will not be stopped.

20 experience points with 2 chains
50 experience points with 3 chains
100 experience points with 4 chains
150 experience points with 5 chains
200 experience points for every 6-9 chains
300 experience points for every 10-15 chains
500 experience points for every 16 or over chains.




<strong class="txt-large">Ring of Zero</strong>
You can obtain this skill by getting the Gold Medal on Skeleton Dome: Rampage.
If you earn Experience Points with an action while you have zero Rings, you receive double the number of Experience Points.
This approach is geared toward advanced players, as the skill does nothing on its own, and the “zero Rings” condition is a very risky one.




<strong class="txt-large">Chain Bonus</strong>
You can obtain this skill by getting the Gold Medal on Night Palace: Rampage.
You will earn Experience Points for collecting Rings in succession.
As in the “Get a X-Ring chain” missions, once the Chain Count begins, you can earn Experience Points by building longer chains within the time limit. This requires a high level of technical skill, but it produces great results on the “Get a X-Ring chain” missions.
<img alt="screenshot_008.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_008.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_009.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_009.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Chains will work by taking the next ring within 1 second from the last one.

100 experience points with 20-24 chains 
200 experience points with 25-29 chains
300 experience points with 30-34 chains
400 experience points with 35-39 chains
500 experience points with 40-44 chains
700 experience points with 45-49 chains
1000 experience points with over 50 chains.

If your focus is to gain experience points, it will be efficient to stop at 50 chains.




<strong class="txt-large">Collection Present</strong>
You can obtain this skill by getting the Gold Medal in the Alf Layla wa Layla battle.
The number of Rings you can collect on a stage is limited to 100, and when you have 100 Rings you will earn Experience Points for distance traveled.
This requires a high level of technical skill, since you must play without making any mistakes after reaching 100 Rings. But if you’re able to use this skill well, you can earn large amounts of Experience Points.




<strong class="txt-large">Sub C-Present</strong>
This is the Sub-version of the Collection Present skill obtained at Level 55.
The basic function is the same as Collection Present, but in this case, the Soul Gauge is consumed when you earn Experience Points. This means that you can’t earn too many Experience Points unless you have energy built up in your Soul Gauge.

]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/03/useful_skills_for_maximizing_e_1.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/03/useful_skills_for_maximizing_e_1.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Strategies</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 06:00:21 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Maximum scores for the first long courses in each world</title>
         <description><![CDATA[The first mission you play in each world has the longest course in that world, and strategy plays an important role. For players with enough skill, these are great opportunities to collect points.




<strong class="txt-large">Sand Oasis</strong>
“Find King Shahryar!”
Mission difficulty: Low
Score of 5000 with time around 4:30 (Silver Medal)
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">Dinosaur Jungle</strong>
“Follow the Pterosaur!”
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 4000 with time around 4:40 (Silver Medal)
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">Evil Foundry</strong>
“Head for the center!”
Mission difficulty: High
Score of 8000 with time around 5:00 (Silver Medal)
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">Levitated Ruin</strong>
“Find Sinbad!”
Mission difficulty: High
Score of 8500 with time around 6:00 (Silver Medal)
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">Pirate Storm</strong>
“Follow the pirates!”
Mission difficulty: High
Score of 9000 with time around 7:30 (Bronze Medal)
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">Skeleton Dome</strong>
“Find King Solomon!”
Mission difficulty: High
Score of 13000 with time around 7:30 (Bronze Medal)
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">Night Palace</strong>
“Sneak into the palace!”
Mission difficulty: High
Score of 12000 with time around 7:00 (Bronze Medal)

]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/03/maximum_scores_for_the_first_l.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/03/maximum_scores_for_the_first_l.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Strategies</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 05:53:59 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Earning Experience Points</title>
         <description><![CDATA[To earn more skills, you must level up. To do that, you need to earn as many Experience Points as possible. This section will list stages and skills that you can take advantage of to earn Experience Points quickly.

<strong class="txt-large">[Stages you can use to earn Experience Points quickly]</strong>
The Total Score number on each mission’s results screen (the combination of the Action Bonus, Enemy Bonus, Ring Bonus and Technical Bonus) is directly linked to your Experience Points, so the missions below are those that allow you to earn higher scores in relatively short times.
* All scores assume no damage (Technical Bonus × 2)




<strong class="txt-large">Lost Prologue</strong>
<strong>Time Attack 1</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 4000 with time around 1:30
<strong>Time Attack 2</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 4000 with time around 1:30
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">Sand Oasis</strong>
<strong>Don’t break the jar!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Low
Score of 2000 with time around 1:20
<strong>Don’t get defeated!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Low
Score of 2000 with time around 1:30
<strong>Finish within 120 seconds!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Low
Score of 2500 with time around 1:30
<strong>Defeat 20 Enemies!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Low
Score of 3000 with time around 1:30
<strong>Battle! Sand Scorpion!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Low
Score of 2000 with time around 1:00
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">Evil Foundry</strong>
<strong>Defeat 20 Enemies!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 3500 with time around 1:10
<strong>Battle! IfritGolem!</strong>
Mission difficulty: High
Score of 7000 with time around 3:00
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">Pirate Storm</strong>
<strong>Beat Uhu to the Goal!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 2500 with time around 1:30
<strong>Defeat 20 Enemies!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 4000 with time around 2:00
<strong>Finish within 100 seconds!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 3000 with time around 1:40
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">Skeleton Dome</strong>
<strong>Don’t take damage!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 3000 with time around 1:10
<strong>Don’t get defeated!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 2000 with time around 1:20
<strong>Defeat 15 Enemies!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 2000 with time around 1:30
<strong>Collect 50 Rings!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 2500 with time around 1:00
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">Night Palace</strong>
<strong>Beat Uhu to the goal!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 2500 with time around 1:20
<strong>Defeat 20 Enemies!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 4500 with time around 2:10
<strong>Collect 100 Rings!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 2000 with time around 1:00
<strong>Get a 100-Ring chain!</strong>
Mission difficulty: Medium
Score of 2000 with time around 1:00
<strong>Don’t take damage!</strong>
Mission difficulty: High
Score of 2000 with time around 1:10
<strong>Battle! Erazor Djinn!</strong>
Mission difficulty: High
Score of 9000 with time around 3:00
<strong>Last Chapter!</strong>
Mission difficulty: High
Score of 8000 with time around 3:00
]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/03/earning_experience_points.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/03/earning_experience_points.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Strategies</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2007 05:34:24 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Mission Conditions and Effective Skills</title>
         <description><![CDATA[Each world contains several missions that have the same conditions as those in other worlds. For missions with the same conditions, the same set of skills is often effective. An explanation of those mission conditions and effective skills follows.




<strong class="txt-large">“Defeat Enemies !” missions</strong>
You can clear these missions by defeating the set number of Enemies.
You can use Homing Attack as your primary attack most of the time, but using skills like Fire Gaze, Fire Tackle and Volcano Slider that add attack damage to normal moves lets you proceed more efficiently.
<img alt="screenshot_067.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_067.jpg" width="260" height="195" />Fire Gaze

<img alt="screenshot_059.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_059.jpg" width="260" height="195" />Fire Tackle

<img alt="screenshot_071.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_071.jpg" width="260" height="195" />Volcano Slider
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">“Don’t defeat enemies!” mission</strong>
<img alt="screenshot_003x.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_003x.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
You can clear these missions by making it through the stage without defeating any Enemies. Areas where you can run right by enemies aren’t too difficult, but when enemies block your path you need to jump to avoid them. And since lock-on cursors still appear, it’s all too easy to do a Homing Attack by mistake.
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">“Don’t get defeated!” mission</strong>
You can clear these missions by making it to the goal without falling or taking damage when you have no Rings. Skills that help you avoid losing Rings, like Ring Bonus and Ring Saver, are useful here.
<img alt="screenshot_028.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_028.jpg" width="260" height="195" />Ring Saver
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">“Collect Rings!” mission</strong>
You can clear these missions by collecting the set number of Rings. To save time, equip Ring Bonus so you can start with a few more Rings at the beginning of the mission. 
<img alt="screenshot_004.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_004.jpg" width="260" height="195" />Ring Bonus
In the “Use Back Step to collect 10 Rings” mission in the Lost Prologue, however, the Ring Bonus Rings won’t count, since only Rings collected with Back Step are counted.
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">“Beat Uhu to the goal!” mission</strong>
<img alt="screenshot_010.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_010.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
You can clear these missions by making it to the goal before the blue, glowing Uhu. These are racing missions, so choose your skills with an emphasis on speed, and use Speed Break to jump ahead of the competition.
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">“Finish within X seconds!” mission</strong>
You can clear these missions by making it to the goal within the allotted time limit. These missions are similar to time attacks in a racing game, so choose your skills with an emphasis on speed, and use Speed Break to blast through portions of the stage and cut your time.
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">“Don’t get any Pearls!” mission</strong>
<img alt="screenshot_019x.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_019x.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
You can clear these missions by making it to the goal without picking up any Pearls. Even if you don’t have any skills equipped, Pearls are slightly attracted to Sonic, so very precise controls will be required.
Since you cannot collect Pearls, you will be unable to charge the Soul Gauge and use Time Break. As a result, you will need to use Quick Step-type skills, Full Break and Charge Jump (to take advantage of the stopped state while charging) to help you maintain a high level of control.
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">“Don’t take damage!” mission</strong>
You can clear these missions by making it to the goal without taking damage even once.
You cannot take damage, so using speed-type skills is risky. It will be important to use Time Break well to maintain precise control.
<img alt="screenshot_047.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_047.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
Also, advanced players can take advantage of Aegis Slider’s invincibility while sliding, the Skimmer-type skills’ lengthened sliding distance, and the Slide-type skills’ improved movements while sliding.
<img alt="screenshot_033.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_033.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">“Finish with 0 Rings!” mission</strong>
You can clear these missions by arriving at the goal carrying zero Rings—this doesn’t mean that you cannot collect any Rings during the mission. No matter how many Rings you collect, you can take damage from Enemies or traps to get rid of them, and still clear the mission with relative ease.
<img alt="screenshot_052.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_052.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_053.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_053.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
If you’re trying to get a good score, however, advanced players can equip Ring Exchange to convert collected Rings into Pearls.
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
<strong class="txt-large">“Get an X-Ring chain!” mission</strong>
You can clear these missions by collecting a set number of Rings in a chain. To create a chain of rings, you must first collect 20 Rings in a row. After you collect 20 Rings the counter will start, but unless you pick up the next Ring before the time limit shown on the screen, the count will end, and the chain will be broken. You must then start over unless you have already collected the required number of Rings.
To collect Rings in a row, useful tactics include using Speed Break to collect large swaths of Rings at once, or using Time Break to make sure you don’t miss any Rings. 
<img alt="screenshot_064.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_064.jpg" width="260" height="195" /><img alt="screenshot_056.jpg" src="http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/jp/images/screenshot_056.jpg" width="260" height="195" />
One thing to watch out for: even after you have collected the required number of Rings, the mission will continue as long as you keep collecting Rings. To get the best possible time, make sure you stop collecting Rings as soon as you reach the required number.





<strong class="txt-large">Super Play</strong>
<strong>PIRATE STORM
Chain of Rings "Get a 100-Ring Chain!"</strong>
<object width="425" height="350"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/m04mgozTMuw"></param><param name="wmode" value="transparent"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/m04mgozTMuw" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" wmode="transparent" width="425" height="350"></embed></object>
You need 100 chains to complete the mission, 
but this gameplay shows you how to take over 200 chains.
]]></description>
         <link>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/03/mission_conditions_and_effecti_1.html</link>
         <guid>http://www.sonicteam.com/secretrings/en/2007/03/mission_conditions_and_effecti_1.html</guid>
                  <category domain="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#category">Advanced Strategies</category>
        
        
         <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2007 05:19:51 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
      
   </channel>
</rss>
