<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
      <title>International CES News</title>
      <link>http://www.CESweb.org</link>
      <description>Stay up-to-date on the latest developments for 2008 International CES attendees.</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 19:24:49 UTC</pubDate>
      <docs>http://www.CESweb.org/docs</docs>
      <generator>RedDot CMS 6.1.1.18</generator>
<image>
<title> </title>
<url>
<img src="http://stats.indextools.com/p.pl?a=1000217290027" />
</url>
<link>http://www.CESweb.org</link>
<width>1</width>
<height>1</height>
</image>


      <item>
         <!--/A46663861A3D41398B289C0255907957.htm-->
         <title>CES posts 12 percent attendance growth</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3837</link> 
         <description>Independent audit verifies more than 126,000 industry professionals at the 2010 CES.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 05:24:07 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3837</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/3E9B91BF4F854B47894FAA0AAC1DA8B8.htm-->
         <title>AHAM and CES join forces to showcase smart appliances in Connected Home Appliances TechZone</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3834</link> 
         <description>The Consumer Electronics Association (CEA)® today announced the launch of the Connected Home Appliances TechZone at the 2011 International CES,  the world’s largest consumer technology tradeshow. </description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 6 May 2010 15:56:44 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3834</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/A1907572DED84DE8A889B5A4ECA1F47D.htm-->
         <title>New Telecom Pavilion slated for 2011 to feature manufacturers of advanced broadband equipment</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3833</link> 
         <description>Global telecom buyers meet next generation broadband infrastructure solutions at 2011 CES</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 6 May 2010 15:47:31 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3833</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/AFEEED799CA94248A507858DF03E9665.htm-->
         <title>Hip, new hotel offers deep discounts for CEA Line Shows exhibitors</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3829</link> 
         <description>Located on 37th and Lexington Ave. in New York City, the hotel is nearby the June event.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 10:25:38 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3829</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/33EB8925D29D4B72AE30D2B325740455.htm-->
         <title>Respected journalists, analysts and economists fill CEA Line Shows' speaker lineup</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3828</link> 
         <description>The New York City location and important mid-year timing are ideal for NYC-area media looking to experience the latest technology products to feature in summer vacation, back to school and holiday gift-giving previews.</description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 15:48:21 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3828</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/F1C7762F9520486A91DD47075F4FC66F.htm-->
         <title>CEA Line Shows, the CE industry’s official mid-year tech showcase, returns to N.Y.C.  June 22</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3820</link> 
         <description>Attend manufacturer line shows for media and dealers, press conferences with key industry analysts and an innovation-focused conference program chaired by CBS/CNET correspondent Natali Del Conte.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 9 Mar 2010 10:09:18 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3820</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/D94F20AC7A7A4A8882F7380ED5CDE60E.htm-->
         <title>2011 CES iLOUNGE Pavilion doubles, will feature largest display of iPod, iPhone, iPad AND Mac products in CES history</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3811</link> 
         <description>Exhibit space expands for 2011 CES due to industry demand</description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 3 Feb 2010 09:32:52 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3811</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/BA3ACE02B66A433EA83D8BE16C6FB802.htm-->
         <title>For 2011, consider exhibiting in a TechZone</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3808</link> 
         <description>themed areas featuring hot products, technologies and solutions such green technologies, social media, mobile applications, iPhone, iPod and Mac-specific products, 3D displays, NetBooks, eBooks and other emerging technologies.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 08:25:57 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3808</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/A49CD4B420A64F078A37A75BB06E05EF.htm-->
         <title>Panasonic 3D HDTV wins CNET Best of CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3798</link> 
         <description>CNET's expert editors hit the deck running at the 2010 International CES to find the best, new products.</description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 9 Jan 2010 11:13:52 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3798</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/9F6D1E5F9B9245B39ACA64FEE259A6D2.htm-->
         <title>CEA's Shapiro says CE industry will return to revenue growth in 2010</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3797</link> 
         <description>At 2010 CES, Shapiro speaks passionately about the need for innovation to drive the economy forward through its positive impact on consumers' lives.</description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 9 Jan 2010 06:27:47 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3797</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/15BCD090481F450BB4F04E3E5003168D.htm-->
         <title>Avoid airport delays with Bags to Go</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3796</link> 
         <description>If you are flying Delta, Frontier, Southwest Airlines, United Airlines, or US Airways, Bags to Go is a convenient service that has been implemented at The Venetian, the Luxor hotel and the Las Vegas Convention Center (LVCC). </description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 9 Jan 2010 17:58:38 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3796</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/61928E6A4B5845AD81732C6D4310B124.htm-->
         <title>Vegas properties offer discounts and coupons to CES attendees</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3795</link> 
         <description>Looking for a deal on a Vegas show? Want that all-you-can-eat buffet at half the price? Here you go.</description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 9 Jan 2010 17:51:51 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3795</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/724E117C3BF14761BB9FC345BA0FEC99.htm-->
         <title>Head to the Tempo Lounge at Hilton for CES Tweetup Friday Night</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3794</link> 
         <description>International CES Twitter followers  are invited to meet the CEA Social Media Team and other members of our online community at the Official CES Tweetup, hosted by the Las Vegas Hilton. </description>
         <pubDate>Fri, 8 Jan 2010 06:05:58 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3794</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/5B31E6D82CEE4CBC814235A02037D44E.htm-->
         <title>Emmy Awards Tonight at CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3793</link> 
         <description>The National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences (NATAS) has presented the Emmy (r) Awards for Outstanding Achievement in Engineering /Technical Development since 1948. For the fourth year, the Awards will be presented at the International CES.</description>
         <pubDate>Fri, 8 Jan 2010 17:59:18 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3793</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/94D29B1CDF70479C9A17191B478FC79C.htm-->
         <title>CES TechZones: See What is Driving the Digital Economy</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3792</link> 
         <description>Located throughout the entire CES show floor, TechZones are popular, themed areas that draw you in and surround you with emerging products.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 7 Jan 2010 09:47:23 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3792</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/7F88E704BCB44B02844A055397B1749F.htm-->
         <title>2010 CES features record 300 new exhibitors as world's largest consumer tech tradeshow</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3788</link> 
         <description></description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2009 08:39:33 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3788</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/8592D4C44AF64A9289CB1A423600DF5F.htm-->
         <title>In-vehicle technology revs up for the 2010 CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3768</link> 
         <description>CES, the world's largest consumer technology tradeshow, will showcase the latest in-vehicle technology, including an opening keynote by Ford president and chief executive officer, Alan Mulally, with the 2010 Ford Taurus as the show's official car. </description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 07:38:05 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3768</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/60325B1DE64A452080997372BBAB483F.htm-->
         <title>CES renews commitment to be world's largest environmentally friendly tradeshow</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3753</link> 
         <description>Partners with EarthEra to offset emissions from show facilities; donates electric vehicles to Las Vegas police.</description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 08:56:27 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3753</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/865B9E28585C4194BDF55A02BF1EC226.htm-->
         <title>SuperSessions feature FCC chairman, technology leaders and top retail executives</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3725</link> 
         <description>CES conference sessions to address technology policy, the global retail market, safe driving and future innovation.</description>
         <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 17:14:59 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3725</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/8FC141295BAB43DB960AD7ECE6C3954F.htm-->
         <title>New conference programs and exhibits added for content executives</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3724</link> 
         <description>The 2010 International CES is rolling out an expanded lineup of entertainment technology attractions to address growing demand from Hollywood and the content community for exhibits, conference sessions and more.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 06:03:39 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3724</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/94705D1CD4494E4B90184E42FFC63708.htm-->
         <title>West Coast tech companies have big presence at upcoming CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3644</link> 
         <description>Nearly 600 West Coast US-based companies to exhibit CES in Las Vegas this January.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 7 Dec 2009 17:31:36 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3644</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/CD69D331E9A14C139E02EE4C2D37932D.htm-->
         <title>A New Place to Eat and Meet: Bistro CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3625</link> 
         <description>Bistro CES provides an excellent opportunity for uninterrupted, face-to-face time with your customers and business colleagues coupled with a private, well-catered dining experience right on the show floor. </description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 1 Dec 2009 15:39:59 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3625</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/1C21D429FBF14CB1B1C14A2BA030CB14.htm-->
         <title>International Technology Companies Bring Worldwide Focus to the 2010 CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3622</link> 
         <description>More than 950 international exhibitors participating in the world's largest consumer technology tradeshow.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 07:18:47 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3622</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/B03DF462376144C58971A5EC4D3C4D1B.htm-->
         <title>Sustainable Planet: Technology that literally changes the world</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3618</link> 
         <description>The Susainable Planet CE Spotlight at the upcoming 2010 CES serves as the premier location for world-changing technologies, whether benefiting the environment, utilizing new forms of sustainable energy and renewing our resources.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 17:03:30 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3618</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/E35740B615CA4B8FA8AC59B652E60D84.htm-->
         <title>“Into Tomorrow” was born at CES!</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3539</link> 
         <description>Fifteen years ago, the nationally syndicated consumer electronics radio show “Into Tomorrow with Dave Graveline” made their very first broadcast from the International CES. </description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2009 17:05:48 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3539</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/81991B3CB1FF4898941C5ADBE2395731.htm-->
         <title>CES Exhibitor video competition, Visit Me at CES, extended to Nov. 20</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3536</link> 
         <description>Win a month's worth of free exposure on CESweb.org. </description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 08:14:33 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3536</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/D60675E8BBE64276974747821F9D8718.htm-->
         <title>Best of Innovations 2010 Design and Engineering Honorees announced</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3531</link> 
         <description>The Best of Innovations awards are given to the most honored products across 36 different categories, including the new software and online content categories of: electronic gaming software, online audio/video content delivery, online retail and more.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 07:30:54 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3531</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/4AE638EE629D4D4A8E50E39EFC9ED46E.htm-->
         <title>New partners and tracks featured in 2010 CES session lineup</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3504</link> 
         <description>The CES conference program unites the industry's most respected experts with conference sessions that address the latest trends, strategies and profit opportunities in consumer technology. </description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 15:37:12 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3504</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/06E486268917487F8E9675B085955E5F.htm-->
         <title>i-stage winner ReNu Solar Energy System awarded $40K and 2010 CES booth</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3503</link> 
         <description>Eleven finalists unveiled their products before a live audience at CEA's 2009 Industry Forum, in Phoenix, Arizona. </description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 15:27:47 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3503</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/9C28AF9F4FA7425FAD0822E42A197AAE.htm-->
         <title>PC Gaming Alliance and Lego Universe to showcase the latest in gaming technologies at 2010 CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3502</link> 
         <description>The 2010 International CES will feature the latest in gaming hardware and software in the largest Gaming Showcase in CES history. </description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 15:20:56 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3502</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/6FEB7744B7BC42D3A68801CA0B1703E2.htm-->
         <title>Free CES registration extended until October 7</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3422</link> 
         <description>To accommodate everyone who wants to attend what promises to be the largest and most innovative consumer electronics tradeshow in the world, CES extends free registration deadline.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 1 Oct 2009 15:54:19 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3422</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/5C32CC76D266449E907780FBE1B2D424.htm-->
         <title>Hisense chairman to deliver keynote address at 2010 CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3336</link> 
         <description>Keynote demonstrates CES' strength as the top event for global companies.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 08:57:24 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3336</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/2FD1C6514EEA4A5C8B2796785578E9E9.htm-->
         <title>eBooks TechZone sells out, additional space added to meet customer demand </title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3335</link> 
         <description>Entourage Systems, Freescale, Interead and Shortcovers to display latest eBook technologies at 2010 CES.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 08:47:01 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3335</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/6DE48C8486784D59A7789D299F448951.htm-->
         <title>Entries open for Innovations 2010, honoring best in consumer electronics design and engineering</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3334</link> 
         <description>CEA Calls for Entries runs August 24 through September 25.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 08:38:17 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3334</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/42E6F00D40B6477F974CDDFC9EE9EDBC.htm-->
         <title>2010 CES puts spotlight on Digital Imaging Showcase</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3293</link> 
         <description>2010 CES to Include ATP, Kodak, Iomega, Tiffen, Wacom and Wynit.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 10:21:58 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3293</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/28F93EA24CE4428D9F7A49CE6C6C9165.htm-->
         <title>Living in Digital Times to highlight technology innovations for all ages</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3290</link> 
         <description>Living in Digital Times, a new spotlight at the 2010 International CES, focuses on technology's impact on consumer lifestyles, from tech-savvy youth to digital moms to seniors. </description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 09:43:06 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3290</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/1E204ED7703A4A8B9B2087FA1AC9A3DB.htm-->
         <title>Top Intel and MIcrosoft execs to keynote 2010 CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3288</link> 
         <description>Microsoft's Steve Ballmer and Intel's Paul Otellini to speak at world's largest consumer technology tradeshow</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 09:35:43 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3288</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/1398479E2D3C4C09A037D2E449CA5254.htm-->
         <title>Final Week to Enter i-stage for a Chance at $50,000 and Booth at CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3236</link> 
         <description>Think you've got America's next top gadget, app or service? Prove it by 5 p.m. EDT this Friday, August 14, for a chance at $50,000 in prize money and a free booth at the 2010 International CES.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 05:25:35 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3236</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/32FC05BFFD3E4B84957DDECD8A94C48E.htm-->
         <title>Exhibit space still available in EHX@CES show floor area</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3225</link> 
         <description>New for 2010, EHX@CES is powered by CE Pro to bring the EHX experience of a dedicated custom electronic exhibition to CES. </description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 5 Aug 2009 16:47:57 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3225</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/58B394396C014B14BD373FDD4F9B8E44.htm-->
         <title>CES Brings in Some of the Most Influential Leaders in Consumer Electronics</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3208</link> 
         <description>Every January, Vegas plays host to the International CES and the 100,000+ attendees and exhibitors that it brings in. However, who exactly is attending CES with buying power?</description>
         <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 09:32:29 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3208</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/28F58697514B41AD968A22109321A258.htm-->
         <title>The Association Behind the Show Launches New Grass-Roots Movement</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3139</link> 
         <description>Innovation Movement unites industry professionals, entrepreneurs and all Americans who believe innovation will promote American global leadership and economic recovery and growth.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 07:55:54 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3139</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/E6CE3665CE104E02B06987A975048D14.htm-->
         <title>Green is the New Black and Other Top Trends for 2010 CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3138</link> 
         <description>Here’s a quick shot at what developments playing out at CES 2010 might emerge as game changers in the years to come. </description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 07:43:02 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3138</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/1E52278DD7F348DBACAD5D9829773884.htm-->
         <title>To Exhibit or Not to Exhibit During a Recession: Use Numbers to Help You Decide</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3128</link> 
         <description>CEA Marketing Vice President Susan Littleton shares her thoughts about why exhibiting at tradeshows is valuable during a recession.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 06:29:04 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3128</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/5FC36BB1630B45468063AF2CBA4CD9AD.htm-->
         <title>Secure Your Travel Visa Now</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3127</link> 
         <description>Wait times for a visa interview can be several weeks or more in many countries, especially during peak travel periods.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 06:22:51 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3127</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/13D9FAF9590E4CF6BEBC2894F0CF9251.htm-->
         <title>CEA to Co-produce the International Forum on Sustainability of Consumer Electronics at SINOCES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3079</link> 
         <description>E-waste and sustainability experts convene at China's most important consumer technology event this July. </description>
         <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 08:25:24 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3079</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/6CB509243E6B469BA3040403C5E85802.htm-->
         <title>Official CES Hotels Now Accepting Reservations for 2010 Show</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3065</link> 
         <description>The only thing more important than registering for CES is booking hotel accommodations for CES. </description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 8 Jun 2009 06:38:59 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3065</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/8CEC340899854720AAC6ADDF78870AE6.htm-->
         <title>Reach More CE Pros Through the Combined Power of EHX and CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3061</link> 
         <description>Exhibiting opportunities are available at the first annual EHX@CES taking place in conjunction with the 2010 CES. </description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2009 14:55:16 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3061</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/6A6EEFD5F3B44437B31FFA985474B600.htm-->
         <title>Aneesh Chopra, U.S. Chief Technology Officer, to Keynote CEA Line Shows</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3060</link> 
         <description></description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2009 14:45:22 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3060</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/9D9420D58A374469987B77E7A22CB856.htm-->
         <title>CEA Line Shows Just Days Away</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#3039</link> 
         <description>If consumer electronics is your business, then register to attend CEA Line Shows, June 10-11.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2009 10:43:56 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">3039</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/D3351770277640CC8BB0F9BC29F9D977.htm-->
         <title>Do You Have the Formula for Success on the i-stage?</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#2999</link> 
         <description>i-stage is the proving ground for next-gen technologies – a chance for the hottest up-and-coming products, coolest services and killer applications to show off their selling points and duke it out to become the most promising powerhouse. </description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 7 May 2009 14:57:56 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">2999</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/9D924B2F52444EADB56B068DACDE9866.htm-->
         <title>Women and Tech Awards, Panel and Reception at CEA Line Shows, June 11</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#2998</link> 
         <description>Sessions unveil the best tech products for women.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 12:14:35 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">2998</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/AB4DCCB3CFB34FB2A163968E80826EB8.htm-->
         <title>2009 SINOCES Hosts International CES' Best of Innovations Product Showcase</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#2996</link> 
         <description>SINOCES attendees get the only opportunity outside the U.S. to see CES Innovations.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 11:16:30 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">2996</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/D065B978EBD7497B8C684BF1BF1FDB45.htm-->
         <title>CEA President Says on CNN.com: The Next Generation Won't Have a Bill Gates</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#2995</link> 
         <description>CEA President and CEO Gary Shapiro provides CNN.com commentary on how the government has been rushing to bail out failing companies.</description>
         <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 08:38:02 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">2995</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/2C4EB1C4ECFC4C99BB285B9947555218.htm-->
         <title>New Customs Regulation Rule Affects CES Exhibitors</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/rssNews.asp#2994</link> 
         <description>New U.S. Customs regulation for ocean freight shipped to the U.S. in place for 2010 International CES shipments.</description>
         <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 16:51:38 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">2994</guid>
      </item>

</channel>
</rss>
