<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
      <title>International CES News</title>
      <link>http://www.CESweb.org</link>
      <description>Stay up-to-date on the latest developments for 2012 International CES attendees.</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 17:37:09 UTC</pubDate>
      <docs>http://www.CESweb.org/docs</docs>
      <generator>RedDot CMS 6.1.1.18</generator>
<image>
<title> </title>
<url>
<img src="http://stats.indextools.com/p.pl?a=1000217290027" />
</url>
<link>http://www.CESweb.org</link>
<width>1</width>
<height>1</height>
</image>


      <item>
         <!--/9196D45D246F4B24B26EAA28320E8A44.htm-->
         <title>2012 International CES Reused and Recycled 75 Percent of Materials</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6330</link> 
         <description>CEA announces record greening efforts at 2012 show.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 14:30:40 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6330</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/C4B81BB0E188468D9B2E77390837DE8F.htm-->
         <title>Take Your Place in the Spotlight with these Major Branding Opportunities</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6329</link> 
         <description>With 150,000 attendees expected at the 2013 International CES, your company needs to stand out in the crowd. Go beyond your booth and put your company in the spotlight with one of the following blockbuster options.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 08:17:24 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6329</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/462B1EA459E84F8B88E42F640892E1AE.htm-->
         <title>Bring Your Business to NYC in June</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6328</link> 
         <description>Taking place in New York City, the media capital of the world, CEA Line Shows is the perfect venue to get maximum exposure at a very affordable cost</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 5 Apr 2012 16:58:19 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6328</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/73722FFD279C4CB894584F42399169EF.htm-->
         <title>CE Retail Revenue in China Expected to Reach $114 Billion for 2012 </title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6327</link> 
         <description>serves as a launch pad for both Chinese and U.S. companies looking to introduce new products into the booming Chinese marketplace.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 5 Apr 2012 16:50:24 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6327</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/C1250CCA80464D2E91FB733C983BBA82.htm-->
         <title>Experts Reveal Key Trends in Consumer Electronics</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6325</link> 
         <description>In a series of insightful SuperSession panels at the 2012 CES, experts convened to discuss a variety of consumer electronics (CE) trends, including 3D content, IPTV, auto tech and more.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 05:08:59 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6325</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/68CCF5CFF1CD4B6497EDA582C835B5F4.htm-->
         <title>From Wired.com: Nine Gadgets for Tracking Health and Fitness</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6324</link> 
         <description>As told by John Bradley, here are the nine of the most interesting personal data-tracking gadgets that the Wired crew saw at CES. </description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 05:07:44 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6324</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/EC2FFE81B6684900A25DC591191BC546.htm-->
         <title>CEA Renews Commitment to Startups and Entrepreneurs with Expanded Eureka Park TechZone at 2013 CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6321</link> 
         <description>CEA renews its partnerships with two Eureka Park sponsors, the National Science Foundation (NSF) and Startup America Partnership, to secure participation from start-up companies that will introduce innovative products at the 2013 CES.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 06:22:42 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6321</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/84315D64E6014601AFF9A6151C15E0AB.htm-->
         <title>Shapiro Brings CES News, Innovation Outlook to SXSW</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6320</link> 
         <description>On Monday, March 12, Consumer Electronics Association (CEA) CEO Gary Shapiro will be attending a variety of events at the South by Southwest Interactive festival. </description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 15:50:46 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6320</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/A4AF97A474044267B63A35939970B752.htm-->
         <title>SINOCES Returns to China on July 5</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6319</link> 
         <description>SINOCES serves as a launch pad for both Chinese and U.S. companies looking to introduce their new products into the booming Chinese marketplace.</description>
         <pubDate>Fri, 9 Mar 2012 17:49:16 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6319</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/ABAB12D8D8704F27803A4E600B9A045C.htm-->
         <title>2012 CE Week Showcases Global Brands and Innovators In NYC</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6312</link> 
         <description>CE Week's conferences, exhibitions, workshops, networking events create one unforgettable week. </description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 17:38:06 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6312</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/EE5464CB2E054EE2B8D1C9BD98C77191.htm-->
         <title>Purchases on Mobile Devices Expanding Dramatically, CEA Study Finds</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6311</link> 
         <description>More than a third of mobile product owners are using their devices for mobile commerce, according to a new CEA study. The same study also finds that, on average, each consumer plans to spend $575 on mobile purchases in the next 12 months.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 08:43:48 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6311</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/9D38CA2EEFA345A1A552AED8DD93973C.htm-->
         <title>A  Dozen Reasons to Mark Your Calendar Before the Next CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6309</link> 
         <description>CEA sponsors a variety of events to educate the masses and unite manufacturers, retailers and market movers.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 06:15:42 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6309</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/4BFC3CC26A4F49B4BF46F79B15ABA041.htm-->
         <title>CEA Applauds New Visa Pilot Program in China</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6308</link> 
         <description>Gary Shapiro, president and CEO of the Consumer Electronics Association (CEA), issued the following statement applauding the U.S. government for its launch of a new Interview Waiver Pilot Program for U.S. visa applicants in China.</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 08:01:40 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6308</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/7B9AA2177EEB4FE8988F92B185A79B41.htm-->
         <title>CEA's Innovation Movement Reaches Milestone of 200,000 Members</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6307</link> 
         <description>More than 5,300 Innovation Movement members signed on to the Movement's "Declaration of Innovation" to signal their support of pro-innovation policies during the recent 2012 International CES, the world’s largest technology tradeshow.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 15:29:42 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6307</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/C1B1788BD83B4D7A81B8EB486D134189.htm-->
         <title>Save the dates April 24-25 for CES on the Hill and Digital Patriots Dinner</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6306</link> 
         <description>The Digital Patriots award dinner will honor Sen. Ron Wyden (D-OR) and Rep. Jason Chaffetz (R-UT) as the year's foremost industry and policy leaders behind the legal and regulatory framework that allows the industry to flourish.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 14:13:52 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6306</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/8AC6442355C247A1B44EFC21668A7841.htm-->
         <title>Attention Start-ups: Now's the Time to Consider Eureka Park</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6299</link> 
         <description>During the 2012 CES, the Eureka Park TechZone launched as THE destination to find budding entrepreneurs, fledgling start ups and home grown innovation at the show. </description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 7 Feb 2012 15:28:54 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6299</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/44051D8A74684ABFBCE5F4EFBDB3CF1C.htm-->
         <title>Take Your Show on the Road</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6298</link> 
         <description>While CES is the main event, CEA offers other ways in which to promote your products and brand. These smaller events offer you the perfect opportunity to get even more industry and press exposure – a great way to round out your marketing mix.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 7 Feb 2012 15:26:37 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6298</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/5099DDFE78B8478D85F87E6C3F26BAFA.htm-->
         <title>Acclaimed Producers and Filmmakers Featured in Upcoming Produced By Conference (PBC)</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6297</link> 
         <description>CES will support PBC events, as well as provide significant new programming opportunities at the 2012 event.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 08:47:33 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6297</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/D9DE0C87CE074D14BC6667C8C35CBE7A.htm-->
         <title>CES Exhibitor Directory Connects You to 3,100 Consumer Technology Companies</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6296</link> 
         <description>The 2012 International CES was the largest in the event's 44 year history, with a record number of more than 3,100 exhibitors across the largest show floor in CES history.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 10:06:14 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6296</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/4130C7519584448198063281CF84FE03.htm-->
         <title>CEA Hails Congressional Decision to Pull Votes on SOPA and PIPA</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6295</link> 
         <description>Association urges passage of OPEN Act to curtail online infringement.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 08:32:13 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6295</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/832A87D384744CC085FE516CB1D683A8.htm-->
         <title>Stars of CES Revealed from What HiFi? Sound and Vision</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6293</link> 
         <description>The 2012 International CES saw the launch of Stars of CES – a new Awards scheme from the world's leading home entertainment buyer's guide, showcasing the music- and movie-boosting heroes of the world's greatest tech show.</description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 10:53:48 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6293</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/02B65759BA834215B7712A18BEA867D8.htm-->
         <title>CEA Website Goes Dark Today</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6292</link> 
         <description>The following statement is attributable to Gary Shapiro, president and CEO of CEA in light of activities surrounding the Stop Online Piracy Act (SOPA) in the House, the PROTECT IP Act (PIPA) in the Senate and the proposed OPEN Act:</description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 16:17:50 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6292</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/0D3C4B0EB2504A93B403E227B6E11514.htm-->
         <title>Walt Zerbe Receives 2012 TechHome Leadership Award</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6290</link> 
         <description>At the 2012 CES, the Consumer Electronics Association (CEA) awarded Walt Zerbe the 2012 TechHome Leadership Award for his 25-year involvement with the custom and commercial audio/video, automation, recording and pro-sound industries.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 06:13:49 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6290</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/757500E5AF4D4347A8FC1A903EA466A7.htm-->
         <title>The Guild Wins Best Comedy Series in Inaugural IAWTV Awards at 2012 CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6289</link> 
         <description>From studio content producers to YouTube celebrities, those successfully creating entertainment for digital platforms are celebrated via 33 categories honoring web series and online talent, in front of the camera and behind the scenes.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 16:24:15 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6289</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/8B55D5571D0F424487A15E7C9EB51625.htm-->
         <title>LG's 55-inch OLED TV Snags CNET's Best of CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6288</link> 
         <description>A team of CNET editors led the way by picking the most trail blazing, innovative and category-defining products at the 2012 International CES. See the Best of CES. </description>
         <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 08:20:19 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6288</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/CD02C09047964AA798A274F9D5FD6F12.htm-->
         <title>Magisto Earns Major Bragging Rights at CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6287</link> 
         <description>Mobile apps were put to the test during the Mobile Apps Showdown at 2012 CES! Apps producers had two minutes to demo their app, and an applause-o-meter measured audience enthusiasm to determine the winners. And the winner is...Magisto.</description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 09:03:47 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6287</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/9968659E9E0F4B5091FA76706B2DC942.htm-->
         <title>Lytro Camera Named Winner of Last Gadget Standing at CES</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6286</link> 
         <description>With unanimous enthusiasm the judges felt that this simple box-like camera – that takes the photo first and then let’s you bring the photo into focus – is revolutionary.</description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 08:34:08 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6286</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/0128564B609849AF8CAE6509171FE6B2.htm-->
         <title>IEEE: International Conference on Consumer Electronics (ICCE) Runs Through Monday, Jan. 16</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6284</link> 
         <description>Organized by the IEEE Consumer Electronics Society, the 30th ICCE, which runs through Monday, January 16, brings you the latest researcg and development ideas and next-gen CE technologies from around the world.</description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 08:14:08 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6284</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/B5CDEDFE402D40AEA2DF6600F41D2D92.htm-->
         <title>2012 CES Grows, Excites and Catalyzes</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6283</link> 
         <description>The 2012 International CES was the largest in the event’s history, with more than 3,100 exhibitors across the largest show floor in CES history – 1.861 million net square feet of exhibit space – and drawing more than 153,000 attendees.</description>
         <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 14:53:43 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6283</guid>
      </item>


      <item>
         <!--/F337DF53621C4EF8A2DCA7229B487270.htm-->
         <title>2012 International CES Sets Show Record at 1.86 Million Net Square Feet of Exhibit Space</title>
         <link>http://www.cesweb.org/news/rssNews.asp#6275</link> 
         <description>Keynotes from Ericsson, Ford, Verizon, Xerox, eBay, YouTube, Facebook Are Mid-Week Highlights of 2012 International CES</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 15:27:47 UTC</pubDate>
         <guid isPermaLink="false">6275</guid>
      </item>

</channel>
</rss>
